环球影业公司
梦工场
埃及 开罗
五年前
您的早餐 索利曼先生
Your breakfast, Mr. Soliman.
我不要哈密瓜
I don't care about cantaloupe!
所有的瓜都一样难吃  -我保证不会再有下次了
Tastes like melon! -It will never happen again, I promise.
-快点 哈比比 你给我回来 -我只是去收拾一下
- Yalla, habibi, come back! - Just going to clean up.
-很快的 -我还没骂完你呢
- I'll be very fast. - I'm not done yelling at you!
环球影业出品
一部梦工厂的动画冒险片
二号位 四号位的信号丢失
Unit two, I've lost camera four.
我们需要屋顶露台的视角
We need eyes on the rooftop terrace.
我黑进来了 好了 美肚鲨 该你上场了
I'm in. Okay, Mr. Shark, you're up.
干得不错 菜鸟
Nice work, rookie.
我在路上了 亚斯敏说我
- I'm on my way. - Yasmin told me
对她不够专注 啥
- I need to be more attentive. - What?
你已经很专注了
You are very attentive.
我知道 我也是这么跟她说的
I know. That's what I told her.
快点 你剪头发了吗
Yalla, did you get a haircut?
我...剪了
I did.
谢谢你的专注 有点帅啊
- Thank you for noticing. - It's very nice.
屋顶安全
All clear on the roof.
收到
Copy that.
呃 他说帅的那个是我
Uh, that was me.
-是美肚鲨哦 -是的 没错
- It-It's still Shark. - Yeah, no.
我听出来了 谢谢
I got that. Thank you.
好了 食人鱼先生 开干吧
All right, Mr. Piranha, go crazy.
贪心蛇 该你了
Mr. Snake, that's your cue.
希望时机是对的 小子
Hope your timing's right, kid.
贪心蛇 对菜鸟好点
Snake, be nice to the rookie.
这是她的第一次行动
It's her first heist.
我就是在为她好 我说话就这样
I was being nice. It's just how I sound.
欢迎加入咱们团队
Welcome to the team.
看到了吧
See?
好吧
All right.
我们… 玩笑结束
We finished, uh, with the banter?
开干吧
Let's do this.
来吧 五
Come on. Five.
四 三
- Four. - Three.
二 一
- Two. - One.
好戏上场
It's showtime.
你好啊 索利曼先生
Hello, Mr. Soliman.
原来是坏蛋联盟
The Bad Guys!
多问一句
Remind me again:
你们为什么不直接从前门进来
Why didn't you just come through the front door?
那样还有什么乐趣 他最爱仪式感
- Where's the fun in that? - He loves an entrance.
别过来 你们…你们这些怪物
Stay back, you... you monsters!
怪物
Monsters?
-他刚才是说我们“怪物”吗 -对 他说了
- Did he just say "monsters"? - He did.
要是我 我可不会这么说
I wouldn't have done that.
你喜欢怪物啊
You like monsters?
那我就让你见识一下什么是怪物 哥们
I'll show you a monster, pal.
不 不  求…求你了
No, no, no, no, no, no. P-Please.
好吧 我算见识到了
- Whoa. - Okay, I see you.
看这个 -不 不 求你了 大坏狼先生
Check this out. -No, no. No, no, please. Mr. Wolf.
哦 宝贝 我想见你想到发狂
Oh, baby, where have you been all my life?
不 不
No! No!
不 不错 不错
- No, no. - Not bad. Not bad.
这…这辆车是独一无二的初代款
This is... this is a one-of-a-kind prototype.
闪闪发光啊
Shiny!
等等 我们费这么大劲就为了这辆车
Wait. We did all this for a car? -
听着 小子 抢劫目的从来都不是为了战利品 懂吗
Listen, kid, the heist is never really about the loot, okay?
而是实力的象征 宝贝 -上车吧
- It's a power move, baby. - -Let's go.
我…我得说 不 不 这
I-I have to say-- No, no. No, this--
它从来没开过
It's never been driven!
别难受
Don't worry.
我们给你带了个小小的临别礼物
We brought you a little parting gift.
我们就是这么有格调
We're classy like that.
我还有礼物么
For me?
这声浪
Nice.
你可真会说话
Ooh, you say the naughtiest things.
坏蛋联盟 2
不 不
No! No!
你们这帮坏蛋 是不会得逞的
You Bad Guys will never get away with this!
无恶…
Go bad...
不作
Or go home.
? You see, steel sharpen steel when it's time for the go... ?
抓住他们
After them!
? Stare every challenge in the eye ?
? We don't play with the soul, no matter what you was told ?
? Every rat find a hole ?
? See, it don't matter what you thought ?
? Yeah, yeah, yeah ?
? We taking everything you want ?
?  Whoa, whoa, whoa ? - ? Now don't forget it ?
? Better know we come to get it and we with it ?
? And there's nothing better ?
? I hope you know to play it smart ?
都给我让开
Get out of the way!
伙计们 看我的
Hey, guys, watch this.
加速
Step on it!
你总是这么飙车吗
Do you always drive like this?
只有在必要的时候
Only when it's strictly necessary.
当然在绝大多数情况下 都是必要的
And it's always necessary.
? And there's nothing better ?
? I hope you know to play it smart ?
? No matter what you thought, you better believe we coming ?
? And if you thought that we was playing ?
? Let me show you something, so then we jump ?
? And we swoop and we dodge every bullet ?
? It don't matter when they pull up ?
? And they try to pull it ?
那里 那座桥 就是出口
There! The bridge! That's our exit!
好嘞
I gotcha.
-食人鱼 看一下后方 -没问题
- Piranha, check our six. - I got it.
一切正常 伙计
All clear, papo.
是坏蛋联盟
It's the Bad Guys!
? Better know we on the clock and it's time to go ?
? Everything is tactical, now enjoy the show ?
? Then we skip and we bounce and we hop ?
? Out of every situation... ?
? See, it don't matter what you thought ?
? Yeah, yeah, yeah... ?
? Better know we come to get it and we with it ?
? And there's nothing better... ?
大坏狼 你还有什么备选计划吗  还是我们就这么死翘翘了
Wolf, you got a secret plan, or are we just dead?
-我一会儿就告诉你 -那个坡道
- I'll let you know in a minute. - The ramp!
-然后呢  -冲过去 我有个主意
- Yes? - Punch it. I have an idea.
好的 新来的 让我们看看你的本事
Okay. New kid, let's see what you got.
? Better wear your seat belt and strap up... ?
? I know the way you see us doing it to 'em ?
? I think you really, really need to shack up ?
? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ?
? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ? - ? It don't matter ?
? Every single time they really try to trap us ?
? And they come from every corner and they really try... ?
菜鸟…
- Rookie... - Wha-bam!
? Better get up out of the way ?
? Because we come and then we pack up ?
? And we taking everything you want ?
? You know you better back up ?
? Let's go ?
? Let's go. ?
耶 朋友们
Yeah, baby!
欢迎加入团队 孩子
Welcome to the crew, kid.
-叫我骇客蛛 -好名字
- Call me Webs. - Ooh, punchy.
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay.
我再也…不换别的车了
I am never driving another car ever agai--
洛杉矶 现在
都是废气 混蛋
Nice carbon footprint, jackass!
真有素质
Classy.
来吧 别紧张 放松 放松
Come on. Easy, now. Easy, easy.
来吧 姑娘 你能行的
Come on, girl. You got this.
哦 嘿 看看这是谁
Oh, hey. Look who it is.
来这里
Get over here.
你们都去哪儿了
Where you been keeping yourselves?
我吗
Me?
太棒了
Oh, terrific.
棒极了
Fantastic.
我的意思是虽然不是每个人都相信
I mean, not everyone believes it,
但 呃 坏蛋联盟已经改过自新了
but, uh, the Bad Guys went good.
我就不赘述细节了
I'll spare you the details,
但总而言之  我们都感受到了做好事的快乐
but in a nutshell, we felt the wag of doing good.
顺便交了几个新朋友…
Made a couple of new friends...
黛安狐
Diane?
你是深红魔爪吗
You're the Crimson Paw?
我们拿下了橘子酱  一个真正的坏蛋
We took down Marmalade, a real bad guy.
深红魔爪
The Crimson Paw!
我 不 不 她才是深红魔爪
Me? No, no, no. She's the Crimson Paw.
还让所有人大吃一惊
And surprised everyone
我们自首了
by turning ourselves in.
是啊 我们当坏蛋的岁月其实过得挺滋润的
Yeah, we had a pretty good run as bad guys,
但有时为了迎来更好的生活
but sometimes you got to give up the thing you know
你必须离开你的舒适区
in order to find something better.
所以我们服刑期满后变成了遵纪守法的公民
So here we are, law-abiding citizens
清清白白 重新开始
starting over with a clean slate,
我们迫不及待地期待社会张开双臂欢迎我们
and we cannot wait for society to welcome us with open arms.
那…那你的求职意向… 呃…在银行工作吗
And-and now you want to work, uh, at-at a bank?
为什么不呢 我最好的回忆都是在银行
Why not? Some of my best memories are at banks.
呃 你抢了我们三次
Uh, you robbed us three times.
是你们这家银行吗
That was this bank?
这里写着你从一只邪恶的豚鼠手中拯救了城市
It says here that you saved the city from an evil guinea pig,
但你就不是一个臭名昭著的罪犯吗
but aren't you a notorious criminal?
是啊 不是
Yes. No.
也…也许吧
M-Maybe?
抱…抱歉 有点紧张
Sor... Sorry, nerves.
我…我的意思是 我…我还能 模仿金枪鱼 模仿得特别像
I-I mean, I-I can also do a great tuna impression.
就好像你在和一条金枪鱼说话 对吧
It's like you're talking to a tuna, right?
嗯 我精通各种操作系统
Well, I'm proficient in Unix, Linux, Windows, Mac
并且流利掌握87种编程语言
and fluent in 87 coding languages,
所以 是的 我绝对够格
so, yeah, I'm qualified.
我明白了
I see.
那么 嗯 你如何解释
And, um, how do you explain
你工作经历中的这段空窗期呢
this gap in your employment history?
我的期望薪资
My salary expectations?
哇哦 这是个好问题
Wow. That's a good question.
以前从没有人主动给过我钱
No one's ever given me money on purpose before.
“擅长秘密圣诞老人探险”
"Great at Secret Santa"?
是啊 那是什么…
Yeah. How does that...
等…等等 别说出来
W-W-Wait. Don't tell me.
泡澡球 薰衣草味的
Bath bomb. Lavender.
如果你看到同事 做了一些违反公司规定的事
And how would you react if you saw a coworker doing something
你会怎么做
that violates company policy?
告密者没好下场  等着喂鱼吧
Snitches get stitches and sleep with the fishes.
不好意思 我能再…
You know what? Can I act--
再回答一次那个问题吗
Can I get another chance at that one?
我想我们已经了解得差不多了
I think we got everything we need.
很高兴见到你 谢谢你来参加面试
- So great to meet you. - Thanks for coming in.
呃 我们决定… 我们决定不录用你
Uh, we're gonna... we're gonna pass.
呃 听着 克雷格  任何想改变的人
Uh, look, Craig, anyone who wants to change
总需要一个起点 对吧
needs to start somewhere, right?
所以我只是需要一个机会
So I'm just asking for a chance.
就一个机会
Just a chance.
拜托
Please?
既然这样 大坏狼先生
You know what, Mr. Wolf?
我这里也许…你知道 如果...
I might-- you know, I might,
如果这里有适合你的职位
I might have something here for you.
我会给你打电话
I'm gonna give you a call.
天哪 真…真的吗
Gee. R-Really?
克雷格 那太棒了
Craig, that's great!
手机号码就在我的简历上 就在那上面
Number's on my résumé there.
好的 呃… 这真是太棒了
- Okay. Uh... - And this has been just great.
你可以放手了 抱歉
- You can let go now. - Sorry.
我不是故意的…
I didn't mean to...
我找到工作了 这太棒了 伙计
I got a job! This is fantastic, man.
哦 对了 克雷格  呃 你知道…
Oh, by the way, Craig, uh, you know...
是的 懂了
Yeah. Got it.
…为了更美好的未来
...to a better future.
三周后 我的下一代 月亮X号火箭将发射升空
In three weeks, my next-gen MoonX rocket will blast off
并部署X3能量电池
and deploy the Power Cell X3.
没错
That's right.
免费无线充电 从外太空
Free wireless charging from outer space
直接充到你的手机
directly to your phone.
-不用谢 全世界 嘿 伙计们 -嘿 -大坏狼
- You're welcome, world. - Hey, guys. -Hey! -Wolfie.
大坏狼 你找到工作了
Wolf! So you got the job?
嗯 我的意思是虽然还不是板上钉钉
Well, I mean, it's not a hundred percent,
但他说他说他会给我打电话
but he said, he said he'd call me.
好吧 你比食人鱼强
Well, you did better than Piranha.
我以为我应该 表现出自信
I thought I was supposed to project confidence.
是啊 但为什么要模仿金枪鱼
Yeah, but why a tuna?
什么 金枪鱼很自信啊
What? Tunas are confident.
你认识哪条金枪鱼不自信的
What tuna do you know that's not confident?
所有的金枪鱼
All of them.
金枪鱼很自信 对吧
- Tunas are confident. - Right?
伙计们 别这样 生活就像飙车
Guys, come on. Life's like a car chase.
你们懂我的意思吧 路上总会有颠簸
You know what I mean? There's-there's gonna be
但困难何曾阻止过我们呢
bumps in the road, but when has that ever stopped us?
绝不
Never.
我们只需要一点时间
It's just gonna take a little time,
但我向你们保证人们一定会接受我们的
but I promise you, people will come around.
就算我们被陷害 替幻影大盗的连环罪行背锅 人们也能接受我们吗
Even if we get framed for the Phantom Bandit's crime spree?
说得也太具体了
That's awfully specific.
谁是幻影…呃…谁
Who's the Phantom, uh-- Who?
你没听说吗 新闻里到处都是
You haven't heard? It's all over the news.
一场为了生存的 战斗正在…
There's a battle of survival for the bil--
幻影大盗昨天袭击了三处地方
The Phantom Bandit hit three locations yesterday,
偷走了几件无价的珍品
stealing several priceless artifacts.
幻影大盗致所有出名 就是因为根本找不到他的踪迹
The Phantom is known for being impossible to trace,
但这一次  他留下了一张名片
but this time, he left a calling card.
等等 那是我们的招牌动作
Wait, hey, hey! That's our move.
没错
Exactly.
警官 坏蛋联盟是重操旧业
Commissioner, are the Bad Guys back to a life of crime,
还是被陷害了
or are they being framed?
就像你留着漂亮刘海的脸庞一样
Just like your face with those fabulous bangs!
谢谢 我自己剪的刘海
Thank you. I cut them myself.
听着 我不能对正在进行的调查发表评论
Look, I cannot comment on an ongoing investigation,
但这么说吧 江山易改 本性难移
but let's just say: once a con, always a con.
所以是不是坏蛋联盟干的 我无可奉告
- So it's the Bad Guys? - I said no comment!
别这样 什么
- Come on. - What?
我们要怎么 重新开始
How are we supposed to get a fresh start
如果发生的每件坏事 都怪到我们头上
when we get blamed for every bad thing that happens?
嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys.
今天的太阳 是不是格外明媚
Isn't the sun particularly radiant today?
你穿的是什么鬼啊 你在喝的又是什么啊
- What are you wearing? - What are you drinking?
加了额外螺旋藻的草本康普茶
Wheatgrass kombucha with extra moss
再加两罐冷榨蒲公英
and two shots of cold-pressed dandelion.
呃 我觉得那些东西好像不该吃
Uh, I don't think you're supposed to eat those things.
哦 你们啊
Aw, you guys.
我真希望能和你们开开轻松的玩笑
I wish I could trade lighthearted japes
再聊上一整晚  但我流瑜伽要迟到了
with you all night, but I'm late for vinyasa.
流瑜伽 等…等等 你要出门啊
- Vinyasa? - W-W-Wait. You're going out?
但你…你刚回来
But y-you just got back.
你知道的
You know how it is.
你以为我这身材是坐着看电视练出来的
You think I got this body by sitting around, watching TV?
好吧 恶心 哦 别等我了
- Okay, ew. - Oh, and don't wait up for me.
今晚可是摔角之夜
It's lucha night.
那 再见…
Well, bye...!
伙计们 我觉得 康普茶把他的脑子喝坏了
Guys, I think the kombucha ate his brain.
嘿 你知道吗 只要他开心就好 对吧
Hey, you know what? As long as he's happy, right?
那你呢 我会更开心的
- And you're not? - I'd be happier
如果我能找到一份工作的话
if I could land one of these jobs.
第一印象很难改变
- First impressions are hard to shake.
哦 那倒挺快的
Ooh, that was quick.
我的意思是 我第一次见你时
I mean, when I first met you,
我觉得你傲慢自大 自以为是
I thought you were arrogant, self-satisfied,
不诚实…
dishonest...
…贪婪 我很确定
...greedy, for sure.
哦 是吗 是什么改变了你的看法
Oh, yeah? What changed your mind?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
哈哈 真好笑
Ha ha ha. Very funny.
说真的 当我们一再被拒绝
Seriously, it's hard
真的很难一直保持积极的态度
to stay positive when we keep getting rejected.
我不确定这样是不是让你感觉绝望
It makes you feel-- I don't know-- hopeless.
我的意思是改过自新是我做过的最难的事
I mean, going good was the hardest thing that I ever did.
和你们比起来  我算容易的了
And compared to you guys, I had it easy.
从来没人知道 我是深红魔爪
No one ever knew I was the Crimson Paw.
抱歉  你刚才说你是
I'm sorry, did you say you were the
深红魔爪
Crimson Paw?!
抱歉
Sorry.
我没太听清
I didn't quite catch that.
好吧 这可是你自己要挑战我的
Okay, you asked for it.
你马上就会知道 为什么他们叫我
You're about to discover why they call me
大坏狼
the Big Bad Wo--
我想我有点飘了
I think I got carried away.
我觉得这对我的面试没好处
I don't think this is gonna help my-- with my interviews.
我不知道 但我觉得这名字挺可爱的
I don't know. I think it's cute.
让你更有个性了 哦
- Gives you character. - Oh.
我是脑震荡了 还是 州长在跟我调情
Do I have a concussion, or is the governor flirting with me?
不能两者都有吗
- Can't it be both? - Hmm.
抱歉 我不该… 哦 不 不
- Sorry, I shouldn't have... - Oh, no, no, no.
我…我其实没 嗯…
I-I didn't really, um...
呃 是啊 因为 你是州长
Uh, yeah, 'cause you're the governor,
而我 你知道的 -我有前科
- and I'm, you know. - An-an ex-con.
是的 我懂
- Yeah. - I know.
形象问题
It's optics.
完全是 我们就…
- Totally. - Let's just...
-是啊 就保持朋友关系吧 -保持朋友关系
- Yeah, let's keep it friendly. - ...keep it friendly.
-普通朋友么 -是的
- Medium friendly? - Yeah.
州长女士 哎呀
- Madam Governor. - Oops.
州长女士
Madam Governor.
抱歉打扰 和您熟人…
Sorry to interrupt you and your acquaintance...
她终于记住我名字了
Finally, she remembers my name.
…但您20分钟后还有儿童医院的筹款活动
...but you've got the children's hospital fundraiser in 20 minutes.
我马上就到 莫琳 哦 好的 谢谢
- I'll be right there, Maureen. - Oh, good. Thank you.
又一个筹款活动
Another fundraiser?
哦 看看你
Oof, look at you.
下周这个时间呢
Same time next week?
我都有空
My calendar's wide open.
我知道这很难  但你还是要有希冀 好吗
I know it's tough, but you can't lose hope, okay?
人们确实想信任你
People do want to trust you.
你只需要给他们一个理由
You just have to give them a reason.
你保证
Promise?
以州长的名义保证
Governor's word.
但在此之前 我建议你 练练你的右勾拳
But until then, I would work on that right hook.
感觉有点像被蝴蝶亲了一下的触感
It feels a little like I'm getting kissed by a butterfly.
回头见 硬汉
Catch you later, tough guy.
我那是手下留情了
I was holding back.
“给他们一个理由 ”
"Give them a reason."
我不
No!
我说无可奉告
I said no comment!
我想要答案
I want answers.
给我调监控录像  查通话记录
Get me security footage, scour the phone logs,
我的咖啡呢
and where's my coffee?!
呃 警官 现在不行
- Uh, Commissioner? - Not now!
但你有访客 让他们等着
- But you have a visitor. - They can wait.
呃 但他 呃…
Uh, but he's, uh...
嘿嘿 警长
Hey-hey, Chief!
我能说
Can I just say:
喜欢你的刘海吗
love the bangs.
首先  我现在是局长
First off, it's "Commissioner" now.
其次…
And second...
哦 不错嘛 可是那有什么区别呢
Ooh, nice. What's the difference?
嗯 警长是一线警官中级别最高的 而局长
Well, the chief is the top uniformed , whereas--
我为什么要跟你解释这个
Why am I explaining this to you?!
你动了我的线索板
Did you touch my board?
-我的线索板 我精致的线索板 -哦 抱歉
- My board. My beautiful board. - Oh, I'm sorry.
我仿佛听到你的线索板在说  快点破案
I thought I heard it say, "Solve me."
大坏狼 听着
- Wolf. - Listen.
我觉得我们都有打造形象的需求
I think we're both having an optics problem.
你需要向公众证明
You need to show the world
这次调查都很顺利you've got this investigation under control,
而我们需要向全世界都知道我们已经是好人
and we need to show the world we're good.
如果我帮你抓住大盗  那就是双赢
If I help you catch the Bandit, it's a win-win.
我要给州长打电话
I'm calling the governor.
打吧 这全是她的主意
Go ahead. It was basically her idea.
看这儿
Look at this.
每次抢劫都发生在三分钟的时间窗口内
Each of the robberies occurred within a three-minute window.
所以呢 这三分钟时间就是安保控制台
- So? - Three minutes is the loop rate
循环速率的刷新频率
of most standard security consoles,
这意味着不管是谁干的…
which means whoever did this...
从内部黑进了安保系统
Patched into security from the inside.
对
Bingo.
好吧
Fine.
就算他们做到了 我们怎么抓到他们呢
Let's say they did. How would we even trace that?
我们需要高科技的电脑专家
We'd need some kind of high-tech computer expert.
他们必须寻觅出攻击的IP地址 并将视频流重定向
They'd have had to clone the IP address and redirect the feed
到一个4GHz的虚拟控制台
to a four gigahertz dummy console, duh.
你的大盗都很聪明
Your Bandit is clever
但没他自己想的那么聪明
but not as clever as he thinks he is.
但要完成这些他还是需要一个内应
However, he'd still need an inside man.
拿着这个
Hold this.
看那
There!
那只是个清洁工
But that's just the janitor.
在没受过训练的人眼里确实如此
Perhaps to the untrained eye,
但如果他真的只是个清洁工
but if he's really just the janitor,
他为什么推着一个空桶
why is he pushing around an empty bucket?
所以真正的问题是 他是怎么进去的
So the real question is: How did he get in?
我会从这边过来 卡住风扇
I'd come this way, jam the fan,
撬开格栅  然后砰 就进去了
pop the grate, and bam, you're in.
这里面为什么有酸黄瓜
Why is there pickles in this?
因为那是我午餐
Because that's my lunch.
谁让你吃我午餐的
Who said you could eat my lunch?
是他说这里管饭
Well, he said there was lunch.
警长 拜托 我们专心点
Chief, come on. Let's focus.
我们知道了作案时间 和作案手法
So we know when and we know how.
真正的问题应该是作案动机
The real question is why.
嗯 你怎么不再多叫些人
Well, why don't you call some more people
来一起帮忙
to barge in and help?
你好 朋友
Welcome, friend,
这里是贪心蛇的语音信箱
to Mr. Snake's voicemail.
今天的灵魂箴言是
Today's advice for the soul:
我们需要把关注点从我们之间差异点跳出来
We must stop concentrating on our differences
而去寻找我们的共同之处
and look for what we have in common.
南无阿弥佗佛
- Namaste. - Ugh.
再见…
Bye...!
他被附身了吗
Is he possessed?
呃 别提了
Ugh, don't even get me started.
我的意思是 有一天他去练瑜伽 做陶艺
I mean, one day he's going to yoga, he's doing pottery.
可是谁会做陶艺 人鬼情未了的演员吗
I mean, who does pottery, the cast of Ghost?
伙计们 伙计们 等等
Guys, guys, guys, guys. Hold on.
啊 他刚才说什么来着
- Huh? - What'd he say again?
“去寻找我们 的共同之处 ”
"Look for what we have in common."
看 重点不是 那些艺术品
Look. It's not about the artifacts.
重点是 它们的共同之处
It's about what they have in common.
它们都是用一种叫“反黄金” 的稀有金属制成的
They're all made from a rare metal called MacGuffinite.
当然了
Of course.
呃 反黄金什么玩意儿
Uh, MacGuff-a-what, now?
嗯 听起来有点像编的
Um, sounds kind of made-up.
金子这东西 如果你不知道它真的存在 听起来也像编的
So does the word "gold" if you didn't know it was real.
说“金子”
Say "gold."
-金子 -金子  -金子
- Gold. Gold. -Gold. Gold. - Gold. Gold. -Gold. Gold.
-金子 -金子 -金子
- Gold. - Gold. -Gold.
听起来确实像编的
That does sound made-up.
哦 现在我总觉得 这词听起来很怪 金子
Oh, now I can't stop thinking how it sounds weird. Gold.
所以现在我们知道 大盗想要什么了…
So now that we know what the Bandit is after...
我们就能弄清楚 他下一步要袭击哪里
We can figure out where he's gonna strike next!
这才对嘛 这才是我认识的警长
There you go. That's the chief I know.
嗯 你最近自己磨磨咖啡豆了吗
Mmm. You grinding your own beans these days?
叫“局长”
It's "Commissioner."
现在离开我的办公室
Now get out of my office.
耶
Yeah!
? Shake your groove thing ?
? Shake your groove thing, yeah, yeah... ?
接下来  我们就上电视领奖章了
Next thing you know, we're on TV getting medals.
用我们的名字命名街道
Naming streets after us.
食人鱼大道 宝贝
Piranha Street, baby.
嘿 听这个
Hey, listen to this.
翻译成英文反黄金这个词的意思是
Translated into English, the word "MacGuffinite" means
剧情工具 真可爱
"a small MacGuffin." Cute.
好的 不太有用  但 呃 你还有什么发现
Okay. Not super helpful, but, uh, what else you got?
最著名的剧情工具是
The most famous MacGuffinite object is
瓜特拉曼戈腰带
the Belt of Guatelamango.
你刚才说的是 瓜特拉曼戈腰带
Did you say the Belt of Guatelamango?
你听说过那个 听说过
- You heard of that? - Heard of it?
那可是摔角王
It's the championship trophy
锦标赛的冠军奖杯
for the Lords of Lucha tournament.
等等 那不是 贪心蛇今晚要去的地方吗
Wait, isn't that where Snake is going tonight?
没错
That's right.
你能想象他在摔角比赛现场吗
Can you imagine him at a wrestling match?
他讨厌人群 还有嘈杂的音乐
- He hates crowds. - And loud music.
还有华丽的服装
And flamboyant costumes.
还有所有让生活有意义的东西
And things that make life worthwhile.
哦 不
Oh, no.
是贪心蛇
It's Snake!
全在这里
It's all right here.
欢乐时光 陶艺 瑜伽
Happy hour. Pottery. Yoga.
都和大盗抢劫的时间一样
All the same times as the Bandit's robberies.
他一直在对我们撒谎
He's been lying to us this whole time.
哦 他真是条有毒的贪心蛇
Ooh, he's such a little snake.
所以他才那么开心 哦
- That's why he's so happy. - Oh.
流瑜伽 我呸
Vinyasa, my butt.
如果他被抓到  他会回到监狱
If he gets caught, he's going back to prison.
我们必须在 警长破案前找到他
We got to find him before Police Chief cracks the case.
喂
Hello?
猜猜谁有两只拇指 留着刘海 还破了案
Guess who has two thumbs, bangs and cracked the case?
就是我 哦 真的吗
- This gal! - Oh, really?
今晚就要行动了
It's going down tonight
在摔角之王 锦标赛上 -
at the Lords of Lucha tournament. -
我要当场抓住那个大盗
I am gonna catch that Bandit red-handed.
我得说 干得好 大坏狼
I got to say, well done, Wolf.
干得好 你超出了我的…
Well done. You have exceeded my...
哥 那是我们唯一的手机 搞什么鬼
- Bro, that was our only phone! - What the thorax?
我不知道 我慌了
I don't know. I panicked!
伙计们 这里只有一个选择了
Guys, there's only one play here:
找到我们的朋友然后…
find our friend and...
把他大卸八块
Tear him apart limb by limb
直到他只记得 痛苦为止
until all he can remember is pain!
哇哦 好吧 我本来是想说救他
Wow, okay. I was gonna say save him,
但 当然 如果有时间  我们也可以把他大卸八块
but, sure, if there's time, we can do the limb thing.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
请掌声欢迎
put your hands together
现任 世界冠军
for the current reigning world champion,
帅哥乔治
Handsome Jorge!
哈哈 是的
Ha ha! Yes!
天使的面孔 魔鬼的拳头
Face of an angel. Punch of el diablo.
贪心蛇
Snake!
我要杀了你
I'm gonna kill you!
妈妈说 我永远上不了天堂
And Mama said I'd never get to heaven.
现在看看我 妈妈
Look at me now, Mama!
我需要 很多芥末酱
I'm gonna need a lot of mustard.
食人鱼 看这个
Piranha, check it out.
一件你的尺码  一件我的尺码
One in your size and one in my size!
伙计们 我们晚点再逛
Guys, we can shop later.
现在 我们需要找到贪心蛇 我们走 来吧
Right now, we need to find Snake. Let's go. Come on.
哦 对 对
Ooh. Right, right, right, right, right.
太多好东西了 现在听着
- It's just so much! - Now, listen.
他可能在任何地方
He could be anywhere.
骇客蛛 搜上层 我找场边
Webs, search the upper deck. I'll look ringside.
你们两个… 伙计们
- You two... - Guys!
真没想到 你们大老远跑来
I can't believe you came all this way
就是为了看我逮捕大..
just to see me arrest the Band--
什么 那是什么 我不知道
- What? What was that? - I don't know.
我慌了 好吗 我就是经常会慌张
I panicked, okay? I'm a panicker.
好了 别再慌了
Okay, no more panicking.
骇客蛛 搜上层 你们两个 去后台
Webs, search the upper deck. You two, backstage.
记住 我们面对的是 一个伪装大师
Remember, we're dealing with a master of deception
他能像水一样移动  像烟一样弥散
who can move like water and vanish like smoke.
他可能在任何地方… 他在那儿
- He could be anywhere... - There he is.
贪心蛇 啊
- Snake! - Huh?
我们什么都知道了
We know everything!
什么 你们怎么发现的
What? How did you find out?
贪心蛇宝贝
Snakey Cakes?
如果我知道你有朋友要来
If I knew you were expecting friends,
我就会多买点玉米片
I would've gotten more nachos.
因为 嗯 我知道 你不喜欢分享
Because, well, I know you don't like to share.
那是真的
That's true.
除非巧心巧克力
- Unless it's kisses. - Mmm.
那时他喜欢分享
Then he likes to share,
对不对 贪心蛇宝贝 哦 是的
- don't you, Snakey Wakey? - Oh, yeah.
伙计们 这是苏珊
Guys, this is Susan.
她是你的人质吗
Is she your hostage?
不
No!
她是我女朋友
She's my girlfriend.
她叫他贪心蛇宝贝
She called him Snakey Cakes!
哼 所以这些是室友
Huh. So these are the roommates.
室友
Roommates?
你刚才说室友吗
Did you say "roommates"?
嘿 我跟你开玩笑呢 胡子哥
Hey, I'm pulling your whiskers, Whiskers.
贪心蛇都告诉我你们的事了
Snakey here told me all about you guys.
等等 等等 我…我只是 想再盘一下
Wait, wait. I'm-I'm just trying to do the math here.
你是自愿跟贪心蛇在一起的吗
You're with Snake on purpose?
嗯 一个长着牙的芒果  口气倒不小
Well, you talk pretty tough for a mango with teeth.
什么 我长得像那样吗
What? Is that what I look like?
哦 她真辣 我喜欢
Ooh, she is spicy. I like it.
我下一个 来侮辱我
Insult me next.
准备好跳舞了吗
Are you ready to dance?
又一场胜利 属于帅哥乔治
Another victory for Handsome Jorge!
乔治 乔治
Jorge! Jorge!
没人能击败 我的帅气
No one can defeat my handsomeness.
现在请出
And now bring down
瓜特拉曼戈腰带
the Belt of Guatelamango!
哦 天哪 是腰带
Oh, my gosh! It's the belt!
给我腰带 给我那条腰带 我爱死它了
Give me the belt! Give me that belt! I love it!
等等 粉丝们…
Wait a minute. Fans...
难道是
Can it be?
是的 看起来 我们有了一位新的挑战者
Yes! It looks like we have a new challenger!
有人有充足杀倾向的人
Someone has a death wish big enough
才会来挑战帅哥乔治
to take on Handsome Jorge!
乔治 乔治
Jorge! Jorge!
Jorge! Jorge! Jorge!
当然了
Of course.
有什么比赢得腰带更好的偷窃方法呢
What better way to steal the belt than to win it?
那是幻影大盗
That's the Phantom Bandit!
哈哈 所以你想要那条腰带
Ha ha. So, you want that belt, huh?
我们得揭穿他
We got to expose him.
我们怎么做
How are we supposed to do that?
我们即兴发挥
We improvise.
那 过来拿吧 猪
Well, come and get it, pig--
他来真的
He means business!
我…我们可以谈谈吗
C-C-Can we talk about this?
这才是最好的摔角
This is wrestling at its best!
别打脸
Not the face.
我真的没 想清楚
I didn't really think that through.
你被鸡刮过骨吗
You ever been deboned by a chicken?
准备好看点暴力场面了嘛
Who's ready for some violence?!
-奏乐 -暴力
" playing -Violence!
暴力吗 好啊
Violence! Yes!
伙计们 摘了他的面具
Guys, go for the mask.
? I said I like it like ?
? Now, I like dollars, I like diamonds... ?
? I like million-dollar deals ?
? Where's my pen? ... I'm signing ?
? I like those Balenciagas... ?
蜘蛛啊
Spider!
现在摘面具 摘了他的面具
Now the mask. Go for the mask!
? I like textses from my exes ?
? When they want a second chance ?
? I like proving ... wrong, I do what they say I can't ?
? They call me Cardi Bardi, banging body ?
? Spicy mami, hot tamale... ?
? Hop out the stu, jump in the coupe ?
? Big Dipper on top of the roof ?
? Flexing on ... as hard as I can... ?
? Told that ... I'm sorry, though ?
? 'Bout my coins like Mario... ?
贪心蛇攻击
Snake attack!
哇 等等 哇 哇 噢
Whoa, wait! Whoa, whoa! Ow!
? I said I like it like... ?
太好了
Great.
现在一起上
All together now!
女士们先生们  这可不是什么摔角手
Ladies and gentlemen, this is no luchador.
是幻影大盗
It's the Phantom Bandit.
她来这里是为了偷 …
She came here to steal the... the...
腰带吗
belt?
看你们这次怎么脱身 坏蛋联盟
Good luck getting out of this one, Bad Guys.
什么 啊
- What? - Huh?
是坏蛋联盟 他们要偷腰带
- It's the Bad Guys! - They're stealing the belt!
抓住他们
Let's get them!
快跑
Run!
食人鱼 你把 腰带摘下来行吗 -我摘不下来
Piranha, will you take off the belt? -I can't get it off!
摘下腰带 我摘不下来
- Take off the belt! - I can't get it off!
我的腰带 我的腰带 抓住他们
My belt! My belt! Get 'em!
警长
Chief.
警长 事情不是你看到的那样
Chief, it's not what it looks like!
我…我相信你
I... I trusted you.
所有人 我们有12号警情
People! We've got a code 12!
坏蛋联盟就是大盗 抓住他们
Bad Guys are the bandits! Mobilize!
是 长官
Yes, ma'am.
我们现在怎么办 大坏狼
- What do we do now? - Wolf!
上车
Get in!
听到讯号了吗 上车
You heard the bird. Get in!
走 快走
Go, go!
哇哦 真险
Wow, that was close.
截停这辆卡车
Stop this truck now!
坐稳了 各位
Hold on, folks!
大坏狼
Wolf!
抱歉
Sorry.
她是不是很棒
Isn't she great?
坏蛋联盟
Bad Guys.
我真是老了 干不动这个了
I'm getting too old for this.
所有单位 所有单位
All units. All units.
嫌疑人正驾驶一辆热狗卡车 向东逃窜
Suspects are headed east in a hot dog truck.
能说得具体点的信息吗
2 Can you be more specific?
嗯 看起来是全牛热狗  也可能是西班牙香肠热狗
Um, it looks to be all beef, possibly chorizo.
我需要空中支援  每五英里设置路障
I need birds in the sky, roadblocks every five miles.
我需要监视每一个汽车旅馆  小餐馆
I want eyes on every motel, greasy spoon,
加油站 汽车站  牛棚 鼹鼠洞
gas station, bus station, cattle station, mole hole,
和80英里内的所有水坑
vole hole and watering hole within 80 miles.
出发
Let's go!
现在是私人恩怨了
Now it's personal.
他们上钩了 就像你计划的那样 老大
They fell for it. Just like you planned, boss.
很好 我们走
Good. Let's go.
嗯 事情搞砸了
Well, that went sideways.
苏珊 你太棒了
Susan, you were amazing.
你从哪儿学到的驾驶技术
Where'd you learn to drive like that? -
我以前是送披萨
I used to deliver pizzas.
因为送得太快被解雇了
Got canned for being too fast.
酷
Cool.
你口气真臭 什么
- Your breath stinks. - What?
你用什么刷牙的  沙丁鱼吗
What do you brush your teeth with, sardines?
这话说得真够损的
That's a burn.
我不刷牙
I don't brush my teeth with anything.
惊掉下巴 呃…
Shocking. Uh...
那可不太好
That's kind of bad.
我很惊讶 你还跟我混在一起
I'm surprised you hang out with me.
要不要来片薄荷糖 哦 太及时了
- How about a mint? - Ooh. That's clutch.
是的 给我两片
- Yes, please. - I'll take two.
呃 你呢 大坏狼 薄荷糖
Uh, what about you, Wolf? Mint?
我不用 谢谢
I'm good. Thanks.
所以 你们俩是怎么认识的
So, how'd you guys meet anyway?
快说 快说
Spill it. Spill it.
好吧 嗯… 嗯…
- Okay, well, uh... - Well...
你来说 -不 不  你来说比较好
You tell it. -No, no, no, you tell it better.
是啊 但你模仿各种声音
Yeah, but you do all the voices.
而且 你模仿得那么好
And, like, you're so good at it.
谁能快点说啊
Can somebody tell it?!
好的 好的
Okay, okay.
这是个有趣的故事
It's a funny story.
嘿 孩子
Hey, kid.
你要吃那个吗
Are you gonna eat that?
什么
What?
? I think I could... ?
弄错了
Mix-up.
? Crimson and clover. ?
她为什么在他嘴里
Why is she in his mouth?
总之 我们就是这么认识的
Anyway, that's how we met.
但…但这跟我们 第一次约会比起来不算什么
But-but that's nothing compared to our first date
当时我们… 呃 不 -停
- when we were... - Ew, no! -Stop!
好吧 好吧
All right, all right, all right.
知道了
Got it.
爱能战胜一切  这很棒
Love triumphs over all, and that's great.
但现在  我们需要关注一个事实
But right now, we need to focus on the fact
那就是全州的警察都以为我们是幻影大盗
that every cop in the state thinks we're the Phantom Bandit.
你不太浪漫 是吧
Not much of a romantic, are you?
别管他 甜心鸟 他有点敏感
Don't mind him, Sugar Beak. He's a little touchy.
呃 他被州长发好人卡了
Uh, he's been friend-zoned by the governor.
我可没有被州长发好人卡…
I have not been friend-zoned by the...
我需要一部手机
I need a phone.
州长女士 州长女士
Madam Governor. Madam Governor.
坏蛋联盟什么时候能抓回监狱
How soon are the Bad Guys going back to prison?
请大家不要急于下结论
Please, let's not jump to conclusions
在我们掌握所有事实之前
before we have all the facts.
谢谢 问题就…
Thank you. That's all quest--
今天的问题就到此为止
That's all the questions for now.
好了 黛安狐
All right, Diane.
是时候止损
It's time to implement damage control.
我来告诉媒体暂时没有别的问题了
I'm gonna tell the press there's no more questions
如果他们有… 等等 莫琳
- for now, and if they have... - Hang on, Maureen.
琳达阿姨
Aunt Linda!
真是个惊喜
What a pleasant surprise.
大坏狼 你在想什么
Wolf, what were you thinking?
大坏狼 黛安狐 听着
WOLF Diane, listen.
我们遇到了一点麻烦
We hit a little bit of trouble.
哦 哪部分
Oh. Which part?
袭击局长那部分
Assaulting the police commissioner
还是在成千上万人面前 偷走一条无价的腰带那部分
or stealing a priceless belt in front of thousands of people?
事情不是看到的那样
It's-it's not what it looks like.
有人在陷害我们 你得相信我
Someone's setting us up. You got to believe me.
我当然相信你
Of course I believe you.
嗯 你可能是 唯一一个了
Well, you might be the only one.
听着 我们现在真的需要 你的帮助
Listen, we could really use your help right now.
大坏狼 我不能撤回警力
Wolf, I can't call off the cops.
现在风头太紧了
There's too much heat on you.
我知道 我知道
I know. I know. I know. I know.
如果你能给我一些线索
If you could just give me something to work with,
或者一…一条线索 一个提示 什么都行
a-a clue, a starting place, something.
我只知道这事跟那个
All I know is, it-it's got something to do
反黄金有关
with that MacGuffinite thing.
-反黄金 真的吗 -是的
- MacGuffinite? Really? - Yeah.
那一直都是大盗的目标
It's what the Bandit's been after the whole time.
我不想把你拖下水  但这是我们唯一的线索
I hate to drag you into this, but it's our only lead.
你能调查一下吗
Can you look into it?
是的 我正好知道该问谁
Yeah, I know exactly who to ask.
是吗 听我说
- You do? - Listen to me.
在我查明真相之前  你需要保持低调
I need you to lay low until I get to the bottom of this.
同时  不要相信任何人
In the meantime, don't trust anyone.
还有 大坏狼… 嗯
- And, Wolf... - Yeah?
我们会挺过去的 好吗
We'll get through this, okay?
希望如此
I hope so.
嘿 我欠你一次人情
Hey. I owe you one.
普通朋友不就是干这个的吗
What are medium friends for, huh?
是的
Yeah.
莫琳
Maureen?
是 长官 取消我的预约
- Yes, ma'am? - Cancel my appointments.
好的 长官
You got it, ma'am.
我得去见一个老朋友
I've got to catch up with an old friend.
好消息 各位
Good news, gang.
黛安狐会帮我们洗清罪名
Diane's gonna help us clear our names.
我们只需要 保持低调 然后…
All we got to do is lay low and...
你
You.
你应该吃那片 薄荷糖的 胡子哥
You should've taken the mint, Whiskers.
你好 老大
Hiya, boss.
是的 鸡仔进烤箱了
Yeah, the chickens are in the broiler.
重复 鸡仔进烤箱了
Repeat, the chickens are in the broiler.
什么 我们…我们在哪儿
What? Where... where are we?
发生什么了
What's happening?
从前有一只大坏狼
Once upon a time, there was a big, bad wolf.
哦 我喜欢那家伙
Ooh, love that guy.
真是个角色
What a character.
他是喜欢挑战现状的狼
He's the one who challenges the status quo,
敢于冒险的狼
who takes the big chance.
没有他 天哪 我甚至觉得我们连故事都没有
Without him, shoot, I don't even think we have a story.
而他们叫他反派
And they call him the villain.
嗯 现在有点颠倒了 你不觉得吗
Hmm. Kind of backwards, don't you think?
我认识你吗
Do I know you?
他们叫我幻影大盗
They call me the Phantom Bandit.
我觉得名字还不赖
Nice ring to it, I guess.
不过你可以叫我凯蒂豹
But you can call me Kitty Kat.
我想你见过我的姑娘们
I think you met my girls.
你们好 我的天
- Hello! - Holy shrimp.
我叫妙算猪
I'm Pigtail.
能痛扁我的偶像们是我的荣幸
It was great honor to kick the butts of my heroes.
你们的屁股比我想象的还要棒
The butts were even greater than my dreams.
她是你们的超级粉丝
She's a huge fan.
犯罪迷
Big crime nerd.
谢谢
Thanks.
我想是吧
I think.
哦 嘿 苏珊
Oh, hey, Susan!
其实…
Actually...
我叫毒舌鸦 呃…
- It's Doom. - Uh...
苏珊只是个假名
Susan is an alias.
-你骗了我 -没事儿 小子
- You lied to me. - That's all right, papito.
-你玩弄了我 -不好 伙计
- Played me. - Not cool, man.
-背叛了我 -嘿 嘿 听着
- Betrayed me. - Hey. Hey, listen.
-这只是工作需要 -你真…
- It's just business. - You're...
阴险 你…
- Shady. - You're...
阴险
Shady.
说出来吧 伙计
Let it out, buddy.
你可真是个完美的女人
You're the perfect woman!
她骗过了贪心蛇
She out-snaked a snake!
如果那不是真爱 那…
If that's not true love, well...
那我就不知道什么是真爱了
well, then I don't know what true love is.
贪心蛇…
Snake...
好吧 凯蒂豹 你…你介意告诉我们来这里干什么吗
Okay. Kitty, y-you mind telling us what we're doing here?
直截了当 我喜欢
Cutting to the chase. I like it.
我们在计划一件大事
We're planning something big.
唯一的问题是 这活对我们三个人来说太大了
Only problem: It's too big for the three of us.
而你们正好需要工作 我们呢 需要人手
You need work. We need extra hands.
都是专业人士 你懂的 身怀绝技的那种
Professionals, you know? With a specific set of skills.
一起干最后一票
One last job.
怎么说
Whatcha say?
我们怎么说
What do we say?
不 呃 简单回答就是
No, uh, is the short answer.
但是 嗯 我们受宠若惊
But, well, we're flattered.
但是 呃 唯一的问题是 你知道…
But, uh, the thing is, you know...
-我们现在金盆洗手了 -是的
- We're good now. - Yeah.
-我们不再做大盗了
We don't steal stuff anymore.
是的 所以如果你们要是能把我们解开
Yeah, so if you can just, you know, untie us,
然后 呃  我们可以自己出去
and, uh, we'll let ourselves out.
我们可以就此收场 怎么样
And we can just call it a noche, okay?
你知道吗
You know what?
我喜欢红色的
I love the red ones.
是樱桃味吗
Is it cherry?
是草莓味吗 我不太确定
Is it strawberry? I'm not really sure.
我分不清
I can never tell.
一种人 你懂的
It's kind of like people, you know?
你以为他们是某种人
You think they're one thing,
结果发现 他们完全是另一种人
but it turns out they're something else entirely.
黛安狐
Diane.
她们知道了
She knows.
你能想象这事 要是传出去会怎么样吗
Can you imagine if this got out?
州长曾是深红魔爪的秘密过往
The governor's secret past as the Crimson Paw?
唷 真是个丑闻
Whew. Talk about a scandal.
她会陷入麻烦的
She will be in the hot bubble water.
所以…
So...
或者我换个方式提问
Let me rephrase the question.
与我们合作 黛安狐的秘密就永远不会泄露
Play along, and Diane's secret is safe.
要是不合作 那么你们 还有黛安狐  所有的美好生活
Or don't, and you, Diane, the good life,
一切都将崩溃
it all comes crashing down.
你们自己选
What'll it be?
好吧 辣妹 什么任务
All right, hot sauce. What's the job?
就是那个任务
That's the job.
那是月亮X号火箭
That's the MoonX rocket.
真的假的
Seriously?
你最好还是相信 姑娘
You better believe it, girl.
为什么要偷一辆车 当你能 偷一艘巨大的火箭飞船时
Why steal a car when you can steal a big, jumbo rocket ship?
我觉得她是认真的
I think she's serious.
你们为什么要偷火箭
Why would you want to steal a rocket?
抢劫从来都不只是为了赃物
A heist is never just about the loot.
对不对 大坏狼
Isn't that right, Wolf?
-这是一种实力展示 -完全正确
- It's a power move. - Exactly.
你懂的
You get it.
他也懂了
He gets it.
好了 来吧 我们有活要干了
All right, now, come on. We got work to do.
那之后我们就两清了 对吧
And after that, we're square, right?
你会把录像给我们
You're gonna give us the video?
盗贼的荣誉
Thieves' honor.
这会很刺激的
This is gonna be gnarly.
好的方面
In the good way.
来吧 各位 我们要抢劫了
Come on, y'all. We're going on a heist.
所以 我们又变坏了吗 还是…
So, are we bad again, or...?
你得佩服他们
You got to hand it to them.
他们几乎 想到了所有事
They thought of almost everything.
几乎 哦 你有办法
Almost? Oh, you got an angle.
我总是有办法
I've always got an angle.
最后一票 在这之后
One last job, and after that,
棒棒糖小姐会后悔她曾见过我们
Little Miss Lollipop's gonna regret she ever met us.
州长女士
Madam Governor?
带我去他的牢房
Take me to his cell.
好 好
Well, well, well.
你好啊 黛安狐
Hello, Diane.
橘子酱
Marmalade.
世界上那么多 最高安全级别的监狱
Of all the super maximum prisons in all the world,
你偏偏走进我的
you had to walk into mine.
哦 我的天
Oh, my.
你看起来真像个胖纸
You look like a balloon animal.
我知道 好吧
I know, right?
今天是训练日
Today was arm day.
所以我看起来 格外壮硕
That's why I'm looking extra swole.
所以 是什么风把你吹来了
So, to what do I owe the visit?
我想知道犯罪现场逃逸
I wonder if it has anything to do with
是否与你那些肮脏的朋友们有关
your mangy protégés fleeing the scene of a crime.
你怎么知道的
How do you know about that?
这是我的工作
It's my job to know.
我是《疯狂的麦克斯纪年》 的主编
I'm the editor in chief of the Crazy Max Chronicle.
还负责年鉴 当然我还是匹克球队的队长
I also do yearbook, and I'm captain of the pickleball team.
说实话 我在这里 混得风生水起
To be honest, I'm kind of crushing it in here.
好吧 那祝贺你
All right, well, good for you.
但你对反黄金了解多少
But what do you know about MacGuffinite?
虚构的反黄金
MacGuffinium Fictitium.
有趣的金属
Fascinating metal.
拥有极其独特的性质
With one extremely unique property.
是什么
And that is?
嗯 我不会就这么告诉你的 对吧
Well, I'm not just gonna tell you, am I?
你忘了吗
Did you forget?
我是因为你的罪行才坐牢的
I'm sitting in prison for your crimes.
所以 告诉你对我有什么好处
So what's in it for me?
我不会给你特赦的
I am not giving you a pardon.
特赦
A pardon?
在匹克球赛季季中吗
In the middle of pickleball season?
不 我有个更好的主意
No. I have a better idea.
你想不想玩个游戏
How would you like to play a game?
你想让我玩什么恶心的游戏…
What sort of sick game do you want me to...
背叛州长的先来
Backstabbing governors first.
哦 太好了
Oh, goody.
好了 各位 听好了
All right, everyone, listen up.
你们每个人都 有特定的角色要扮演
Each of you has a specific part to play.
开锁工具
Safecracking gear!
伪装
Disguises!
欢迎 骇客蛛
Welcome, Ms. Tarantula.
哇哦 这装备可真够专业的
Whoa, that is some serious tech.
呃 我想我拿错包了
Uh, I think I got the wrong bag.
是啊 这似乎不是潜入一个发射场的
Yeah, this doesn't seem like proper attire
合适服装
to infiltrate a launch site.
哦 不
Oh, no.
我们不去发射场
We're not going to the launch site.
我们找到了绕过所有级别安保的方法
We found a way to circumvent every level of security
可以直达火箭
leading to the rocket,
而它就在月亮先生的手腕上
and it's right there on Mr. Moon's wrist.
手表可以控制一切
Watch controls everything,
从前门到任务控制中心
from front gate to mission control
再到发射场
to blastoff.
偷走手表就等于偷走了火箭
Steal the watch, steal the rocket.
唯一的问题是他从不摘下来
Only problem? He never takes it off.
幸运的是我们有举世闻名的大盗
Lucky we have world-famous pickpocket.
我们觉得有个好时机
And we think there's a window.
“耶利米·月亮邀请您 参加他的独家
"Jeremiah Moon invites you to his exclusive,
顶尖的婚礼 ”
state-of-the-art wedding."
你认真的吗 我们要去搅乱婚礼
Are you serious? We're gonna crash the wedding?
哦 我喜欢婚礼
Oh, I love weddings!
我的意思是 你知道 我喜
I mean, you know-- I li--
我的意思是 我喜欢它们 它们挺好的 我不在乎
I mean, I like them. They're fine. I don't care.
无所谓 没人关心
Whatever. No one cares.
嗯…计划是这样的
Um... here's how it's gonna go.
这是一个非常特别的活动
This is a highly exclusive event,
而且有高规格的安保措施
and it's got protection to match.
所以我们必须干的有创意
So, we'll have to get creative.
我有点生疏了 但我保证
I'm a little rusty, but I promise
会尊重地对待你
to play you respectfully.
我的天
Mamma mia!
我的花呢
Where's-a my flowers?
不客气 卡布奇诺 超大杯
Prego! Cappuccino! Extra grande!
水果沙拉 柠檬酒
Tutti frutti! Limoncello!
哦 那个头纱 是中古的
Oh, the veil? It's vintage.
一位公主戴过
A princess wore it.
耶利米 哦 你在这里啊
Jeremiah! Oh, there you are.
月亮戴着一副
Moon wears a pair of
AR增强眼镜  可以识别
AR-enhancement glasses that identify
值得交谈的人
the people worth talking to.
和不值得的人
And the people who aren't.
但…但我可是他的阿姨
But-but I'm his aunt!
那些合格的人可以获得
Those who make the grade earn
与月亮先生60秒面对面的谈话机会 -耶利米
a 60-second one-on-one with Mr. Moon. -Jeremiah.
那是我们的机会
That's our window.
我们唯一的机会
Our only window.
但等到一旦仪式开始
Once the ceremony begins,
机会就没了
it's over.
好了 各位 我已经看到了
All right, everyone. I got eyes.
食人鱼 你可以行动了
Piranha, you're a go.
嘿 克拉伦斯 嗯
- Hey, Clarence. - Huh?
这后备箱里 有点不对劲
Something doesn't look right in this trunk.
哦 怎么了 我…我看看
Oh? What is it? L-L-Let's see here.
哦 在那儿 在那儿 就在最后面
Oh, it's there. It's there. Way in the back.
呃 我什么也 没看到 -是啊 不 不
Uh, I don't see anything. -Yeah. No, no, no.
我想如果你把头 伸进去
I think if you put your head in there.
哦 克拉伦斯
Oh, Clarence.
这里一切正常
All clear here.
钛合金三重弹簧连放
Titanium triple spring release.
我想念你了 我的老朋友
I've missed you, my old friend.
你确定你还行吗  贪心蛇宝贝
You're sure you still got this, Snakey Cakes?
拜托
Please.
开锁就像谈恋爱
Lock picking is like a romance.
开始时 你得温柔 p幽默
You got to start gentle, playful,
慢慢敲开它那冰冷的心
work your way into its little cold heart,
直到所有防御都融化
until all those defenses melt away.
哦 听起来挺有趣的
Oh. Sounds kind of fun.
我们在说那个锁吗
Are we still talking about the lock?
停电了吗
A power outage?
你好 极其迅速的电工
Hello. Extremely quick electrician.
有人叫电工吗
Did someone call for an electrician?
是的 先生 是我
Yes, sir. That was me.
她一切正常 哎呀
- She's all clear. - Oops.
别担心 我修好马上就走  不碍你事
Don't worry. I fix and be out of your lip hair in no time.
好了 姑娘们 玩得开心
All right, girls. Have fun.
我叫骇客蛛 今天由我来负责黑客任务
Name's Webs. I'll be your hacker today.
大坏狼先生 该你了
Mr. Wolf, that's your cue.
别一下子 花光了 听见没
Don't spend it all in one place, you hear?
那是我的工作
That's my job.
嘿 下午好 你好 女士
Hey. Afternoon. Howdy, ma'am.
注意 牛仔
Eyes up, cowboy.
你的目标在十二点钟方向
Your target's at twelve o'clock.
大坏狼 那是我们的目标
WOLF That's our man.
你在干什么 排队
What are you doing? Get in line.
巴克·沃尔福德从不排队
Buck Wolford doesn't do lines.
骇客蛛 这名字起怎么样
Webs, how's my cover ID?
稍等 大坏狼 就差几个防火墙了 -很好
Hang tight, Wolfie. Just a couple more firewalls. -Great.
放松 凯蒂豹 我搞得定
Relax, Kitty, I got this.
大坏狼 嘿 不好意思
- Wolf? - Hey, excuse me.
月亮先生 嘿
- Mr. Moon, sir. - Hey.
快点 快点 快点
Come on. Come on. Come on.
大坏狼 绕过去 然后搞定
- Wolf! - Bypass and boom!
小心 小心
Careful, careful.
让我们对我们这位富有 且有影响力的朋友
Let's show our wealthy and influential friend
表示一点尊重 我非常感谢
- a little respect. - I thank you kindly.
你宝刀未老
You still got it.
现在就是机会
Now this is it.
用假手表换掉真的
Swap the watch for the dummy.
嗯 至少这里还有 文明人
Well, at least somebody's civilized around here.
我叫巴克·沃尔福德 大坏蛋石油公司
My name's Buck Wolford. Big Bad Oil.
但我相信你听说过我 我真是太…
But I'm sure you heard of me. I am just so...
需要帮忙吗
Need a hand?
我上次检查时  你可没手
Last I checked, you didn't have any.
你以前可不介意
You never minded before.
她还好吗 哎呀
- Is she okay? - Whoops.
哦 天哪
Oh, boy.
除非我弄错了  火箭确实需要石油
Unless I'm mistaken, rockets do need oil.
你觉得怎么样
How'd you feel about
建立战略伙伴关系  月亮先生
a strategic partnership, Mr. Moon?
你在我婚礼前 向我提出商业建议
You're coming to me with a business proposal
向我提出商业建议
right before my wedding?
你真是个厉害的角色  沃尔福德先生
You're a real operator, Mr. Wolford.
你还不知道一半呢
You don't know the half of it.
谁授权你 进行眼神接触的
Who authorized you to make eye contact?
哦 不 不
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
沃尔福德先生
Mr. Wolford?
呃… 偷手表
- Uh... - Get the watch!
月亮
- Moon! - Ah!
我的索利宝贝 你的头顶看起来格外的光亮
There's my Soli-wolly. You're looking extra bald.
而你看起来很矮
And you're looking short.
大坏狼
Wolf.
我们以前见过吗
Have we met before?
呃 不 我想我只是长了张大众脸
Uh, no, no. I guess I just have one of those faces.
嘿 总之 月亮先生 呃…
Hey, anyway, Mr. Moon, uh...
你在悉尼上过陶艺课吗
Did you take a pottery class in Sydney?
呃… 先生 时间到了
- Uh... - Sir, it's time.
啊 是的 表演时间
Ah, yes. Showtime.
等等 不好意思 先生
Wait a minute. Excuse me, Mr.--
我能…呃…月亮先生…
Can I just, uh-- Mr. Moon...
不 亲爱的 听着 我从不忘记一张脸
No, habibi, listen. I never forget a face.
我…裸体高台跳水 是那个吗
I-- Naked high diving! Was it that?
哦 你好 是的
Oh, hi, yes.
我能借一步说话吗
Can I borrow him for just a moment?
不行 好吧 非常感谢
- No. Okay. - Thank you kindly.
你搞砸了
You blew the heist!
那家伙 我…我认识他
That guy, I-I-I knew him,
他 他就要 认出我了
and he was, he was gonna recognize me.
美女 美女
Bellissima. Bellissima?
呃 我们有点小麻烦
Uh, we got a slight problem.
谁能告诉马可 一条美肚鲨把他吃了
Someone needs to tell Marco that a shark ate him.
你们是想弄坏这个吗
Are you guys trying to sabotage this?
谁准备好结婚了
Who's ready to get married?
美肚鲨 我是个爱慌张的人
- Shark! - I'm a panicker.
这太过分了 你高兴了
This is all too much. You happy?
我喜欢这个
I like this one.
这整件事都完蛋了
This whole thing's a bust!
你失去了你的优势
You lost your edge.
现在州长要为此付出代价了
And now the governor's gonna pay for it.
嘿 别做什么傻事 好吗
Hey, let's not do anything crazy, okay?
我们会给你拿来手表的
We'll get you the watch.
哦 是吗
Oh, yeah?
怎么拿
How?
简直像个该死的童话故事
It's like a freakin' fairy tale.
亲爱的 你穿这件裙子 真漂亮
Honey, you look so beautiful in this dress.
“大坏狼”
"Big Bad Wolf"?
美肚鲨 该你了
Shark, you're up.
欢迎
Welcome!
欢迎来到这个最 美丽 壮观
Welcome to this most beautifious, majestacular,
不可思议的场合
incredimonious occasion.
他能再 含蓄一点吗 -(通过通讯)：喔
Could he be a little more subtle? -(over comm): Whoo!
对美肚鲨来说 这已经很含蓄了 喔
- For Shark, this is subtle. - Whoo!
好好地给我
Give it to me real good.
我们今天站在这里 为了让这位男士
We stand here today to marry this man--
这位阳刚 雄性
this manly, masculine,
极具男性魅力的男士
manleously maleful man--
和这位完全正常的女士
and this totally normal woman
在神圣的婚姻纽带中… 什么 等等
- in the sacra-nimonius bonds... - What? Wait a minute.
…的神圣婚礼中
...of holy matriminimamony.
现在 请你们 牵手
Now, would you please join hands.
就是他
That's him!
是啊 就…就把那些手牵起来
Yep. Just-just join those hands.
看 看 不用看它们
- Look. Look. - No need to look at them.
来吧 来吧 来吧 就盲目地牵起
- Come on. Come on. Come on. - Just blindly join
那些手 我反对
- those hands together. - I object!
什么
- What?!
亲爱的
Honey-bunny.
索利曼 你以为 你是谁
Soliman, who do you think you are?
月亮 看看 你要娶的是什么
Moon, look what you are marrying!
就是那个 大坏狼
It's none other than the Big Bad Wolf!
新娘来了
Here comes the bride.
啵 这怎么可能
- Boop. - How could this be?
他就在这里 索利宝贝 这真是耻辱
- He was here! - Soli-wolly, this is a disgrace.
有爪子 我看到爪子了 马上把他带出去
- There were claws! I saw claws! - Get him out of here now!
你们要带我去哪儿 有证人
Where are you taking me?! There are witnesses!
我们都看到了 你 啊
- We all saw it! You! - Huh?
别傻站着 嘿 主婚人呢
- Don't just stand there! - Hey, where's the officiant?
哦 谁在乎呢
Ooh, who cares?
绝对是坏蛋联盟 史上前五的抢劫
Definitely top five Bad Guys heist ever!
当那个大个子说 “我反对 ”
When big man say, "I object,"
我差点尿裤子
I almost make pee-pee accident!
对
Right.
差点
Almost.
大坏狼 我…我得问一下
Wolf, I-I got to ask.
你怎么知道 那会成功
How'd you know that was gonna work?
你看 凯蒂豹 每个骗局 都有三个部分
You see, Kitty, there's three parts to every con.
首先 设下诱饵
First, bait the hook.
看
Look.
然后是转折
Then comes the turn.
有反常
Something weird is going on.
应该有人反对 我反对
- Someone should object. - I object!
但如果没有最后的收尾一切都白费了 -什么
But none of it works without the payoff. -What?!
因为偷手表
'Cause it's one thing
是一回事…
to steal the watch...
索利曼 你以为 你是谁 -
Soliman, who do you think you are? -
抓紧了 美人
Hold on tight, bellissima.
…而另一回事就是要成功逃脱
...and another to get away with it.
大坏狼
The Big Bad Wolf!
这是声东击西的艺术
The art of misdirection.
重点不是行动  是分散注意力 明白了
It's not the action, it's the distraction. Got it.
是的 长官
Yes, ma'am.
好吧 我看到你了
All right, I see you.
哦 我爱婚礼
Oh, I love weddings!
好吧
All right!
不 不是那里
No. Not there.
不 也许…
No. Maybe...
哦 好多选择 哦 我的天
- Oh, so many options. - Oh, my goodness.
我们能快点吗
Can we move this along?
耐心点 黛安狐
Patience, Diane.
这是一个充满细节策略
This is a game of subtle strategy
和心理耐受力考验的游戏
and psychological endurance mastered only by
只有最狡猾和最老练的头脑才能掌握
the most cunning and sophisticated minds.
“六岁及以上适用 ”
"Ages six and up."
再说 也不是每天都有州长
Besides, it's not every day that the governor
来聊量子磁性
drops by to chat about quantum ferromagnetism.
量子 等等 你是说反黄金有磁性
Quantu-- Wait, are you saying MacGuffinite is magnetic?
不只是一块磁铁
Not just a magnet.
反黄金是金子的原子逆物质
MacGuffinite is the atomic inverse of gold.
暴露在极高电压下…
Exposed to extreme voltage...
它会导致金电子发生解耦反应
It will cause gold electrons to decouple
并以惊人的力量相互吸引
and attract with spectacular force.
原来它是个吸金磁铁
It's a gold magnet.
哦 开始明白了
Oh, she's catching on.
很好
Very good.
当你都能让金子自己来找你 你又何必要去抢银行
Why rob a bank when you can make the gold come to you?
所有的犯罪变成了零运动
All the crime, none of the exercise.
-谢谢 教授 -哇 哇
- Uh, thanks, Professor. - Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
你不能走 我们还没结束…
You can't go. We haven't finished our...
-什么 -不 但是怎么会
What? No! But how?!
这明明是井字棋
It's literally tic-tac-toe.
把你的年鉴寄给我
Send me your yearbook?
你知道 这挺有意思的
You know, it's funny.
你是第二个 大老远跑来这里
You're the second person to come all the way here
问我关于反黄金的人
to ask me about MacGuffinite.
真巧
What are the odds?
还有别人来过吗
You had a visitor?
我不知道她的名字
I didn't get her name,
但显然我们有个共同的朋友
but apparently we have a friend in common.
或者我应该说…五个
Or should I say... five?
州长女士
Madam Governor.
我需要橘子酱 上一个访客的录像 马上
I need footage of Marmalade's last visitor. Now.
找到了
Found ya.
但我能开车吗 不行 -
- But can I drive? - No. -
这是我生命中 最棒的一天
This was new best day of my life.
你为什么要永远离开 哦
- Why must you leave forever? - Aw.
振作点 黄油猪 黄油猪
- Cheer up, Buttersnout. - Buttersnout?
我一直想要个绰号
- I always wanted a nickname. - Oh.
呃 太好了
Uh, great.
嘿 听着 呃 对于那件事 别有芥蒂
Hey, listen, uh, no hard feelings about the whole,
你知道 假装谈恋爱
you know, pretend relationship
为了陷害你和你的朋友 好吗
to entrap you and your buddies, okay?
别这样 当然不会
Come on, now. Of course not.
我的意思是 说实话  我…我并不
I mean, to be honest, I-I wasn't, uh,
真的那么喜欢你
really that into you.
哦 奇怪了
Oh, weird.
因为你 你看起来挺喜欢我的
'Cause you, uh, you seemed pretty into me.
嗯 那是…
Well, that's...
是吗
Yeah?
那是 你知道 我不想 伤害你的感情
That-- You know, I didn't want to hurt your feelings,
所以 呃 是啊  如果你失望了我很抱歉
so, uh, yeah, sorry if you're disappointed.
哦 不 不是我
Oh, no, no, no, no, not me.
你看 呃 我只有 喜欢你才会失望
You see, uh, I'd only be disappointed if I was into you,
如前所述  我真的没有 好吗
which, uh, as previously established, I was not, okay?
当然
Of course.
否则  这次棉花糖敬酒
Otherwise, this marshmallow toast
就会充满 浪漫的张力
would be full of romantic tension.
是啊 我当然这么做了
Yeah. Of course I did.
大坏狼 哦 真的吗
WOLF Oh, really?
所以假扮新娘 是你的主意
So impersonating the bride was your idea?
当然是 是啊 好的
- Absolutely. - Yeah. Okay.
我雇了你
I hired you.
所以 你的主意 就是我的主意
Therefore, your ideas are my ideas.
真讲究
Classy.
反黄金怎么样了
What's going on with the MacGuffinite?
哦 只是个小小的 科学项目
Oh, just a little science project.
啊 所以你为了科学 陷害我们
Ah. So you framed us for science?
拜托 我必须陷害你
Come on, I had to frame you.
这是唯一能把你 从退休生活中引出来的方法
It was the only way to draw you out of retirement.
总之 你得到了 你想要的 所以 呃…
Anyway, you got what you wanted, so, uh...
对了 你想要那个录像
Right. You want the video.
来咯
There we go.
哦 哦 天哪
- Ooh. - Oh, man.
我…我有没有告诉过你 我第一次抢劫的事
Did... did I ever tell you about my first heist?
呃 没有
Uh, no.
嗯 是银行 珠宝店
Um, was it a bank? Jewelry store?
棒棒糖
Lollipop.
上学的时候 我们有个老师
Back in school, we had a teacher
会给好孩子 发棒棒糖
who used to give the good kids a lollipop.
也许是因为我的爪子或者牙齿
And maybe it was my claws or my teeth,
但她从来 从来没有正眼看过我
but she never, ever looked my way.
这很伤人
It was hurtful.
所以有一天 我趁那个老家伙不注意的时候
So one day, when the old fart wasn't looking,
我溜进抽屉 偷了整整一袋
I snuck into the drawer and swiped the whole bag.
那之后
After that,
孩子们想要棒棒糖时  就来找我
when the kids wanted lollipops, they came to me.
伙计 那感觉太棒了
Dude, it was amazing, man.
我生平第一次  感觉到了权力
For the first time in my life, I felt powerful.
那之后我干了一百多票
I must've pulled off a hundred jobs since then.
你偷得越多 他们就越尊重你
And the more you steal, the more they respect you.
为什么要放弃偷窃呢
Why would you give that up?
你以为你装好人 遵守他们的规则
You think if you play nice and follow their rules,
他们就会看到真正的你
they'll just see you for who you truly are.
但我告诉你 他们不会
But let me tell you, they won't.
万一坏蛋的生活才是你最好的生活呢
What if the bad life was your best life?
我的建议是
My advice:
别再抱有希望  享受棒棒糖吧
Stop hoping and enjoy the lollipop.
你拿到了吗 哦 我们拿到了
- Did you get it? - Oh, we got it.
拜托 我必须陷害你们
Come on, I had to frame you.
这是唯一能把你们从退隐生活中引出来的
It was the only way to draw you out--
全盘招供
Full confession.
真不敢相信 她没注意到摄像头
I can't believe she didn't notice the camera.
我们只需要把这个
All we need to do is get this
交给警长来洗清我们的罪名 -好的
to the chief and clear our names. -All right.
我们成功了 我们成功了 喔 耶
- We did it. We did it. - Whoo! Yeah!
呜呼 -胜利之舞
Woo-hoo! -Touchdown dance!
嘿 伙计
Hey, buddy.
你还好吗
You okay?
哦 呃 没什么
Oh. Uh, nothing.
只是 呃  想象着我的下一轮
Just, uh, imagining my next round
刺激的求职面试
of thrilling job interviews.
大坏狼 这就是计划
Wolfie, this is the plan.
是啊 不 我知道 我只是说…
Yeah. No, I know. I'm just saying...
我在说什么啊
What am I saying?
我只是说 万… 万一我们所有的改过自新
I'm just saying, wh-- what if we took a wrong turn
都错了呢
with the whole going good thing?
你懂我意思吧
You know what I mean?
是啊 但这次会 不一样的
Yeah, but it's gonna be different this time.
“抓获了幻影大盗 ”
"Captured the Phantom Bandit."
那写在你简历上 会很好看
That'll look great on your résumé.
我们会成为英雄的 食人鱼街
We're gonna be heroes. Piranha Street.
是啊 不 是啊 完全是
Yeah, no, yeah. Totally.
我在说什么啊 你说得对
What am I talking about? You're right.
来吧 我们去找警长
Come on, let's find the chief.
走吧 这才像话 大坏狼
- Let's go. - That's my Wolf.
你真的以为那么简单就结束了吗
Did you really think it was gonna be that easy?
该死
Shoot.
嘿 -轻点
Hey! -Watch it!
这里有人很淘气哦
Naughty, naughty.
这些是金的吗
Are these gold?
凯蒂豹 我们能谈谈这个吗 呃…
Kitty, can we talk about this for a second? Uh...
不行
Nope.
那是反黄金吗
Is that MacGuffinite?
你是要干嘛
What's going on?
让我来给你们展示一下吧
How about I show you?
哦 漂亮啊
Ooh, shiny.
吸金石啊
A gold magnet?
还真让你猜对了
You bet your scaly butt it is.
而且这只是个测试品
And this is just a prototype.
在零重力下更厉害
Wait till you see what it can do in zero gravity.
你要把它带到太空 废话
- You're taking it to space? - Obviously.
你以为去偷大火箭干嘛的
What do you think giant rocket is for?
又不是为了科学展
Is not for science fair.
你总不能指望偷走全世界的黄金
You can't expect us to steal
在这里进行吧
all the world's gold from down here.
史上最大的抢劫
The biggest heist in history.
将由我们来呈现
Courtesy of us.
全世界的黄金
All the world's gold?
哦 哦 还有点睛之笔
Oh. Oh. And the cherry on top!
=哇 哇 -你在干什么
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. What are you doing?
那影像 你没必要毁了黛安狐
The video? You don't need to ruin Diane.
让我们 让我们 来吧
Let's-- Let's-- Come on.
我们好好谈谈 问题是
- Let's talk about this. - Hmm, see, thing is,
我已经答应过那个豚鼠 会做的
I promised this rodent that I would.
算是种利益交换吧
Kind of a quid pro quo type thing.
橘子酱 我知道
- Marmalade. - I know.
那家伙真是个怪咖
What a goofball.
但科学邻域算是个天才
But a real wiz with the science stuff.
要…要不这样
I-I'll tell you what.
我们毕竟是朋友  我给你一个机会
'Cause we're friends, I'm gonna give you a choice.
不 不 停下
No, no, no, no, no! Stop it.
你可以用这个停下它
You can stop it with this.
什么…
What the...
上传程序是与吸金石匹配的
The upload is paired to the magnet.
你关掉吸金石  影像就会疯传
The moment you turn it off, the video goes viral.
或者开着它保护黛安狐
Or leave it on, protect Diane,
但你们就一直吊着 直到警察到来
but y'all keep dangling until the police arrive.
真是个两难的选择
Oh, such a dilemma.
警察
The police?
你好 我是局长
Hello. Commissioner speaking.
是的 局长 我有个重要情报
Yes, ma'am. I got a hot tip.
坏蛋联盟躲在
The Bad Guys are holed up in a hangar
月亮X号发射场以北两公里的机库里
two klicks north of the MoonX launch site.
什么 等…等等 你…是谁…
What? W-Wait. Wh-Who is...
抱歉 宝贝
Sorry, doll.
听着 这不是个人恩怨
Look, it's nothing personal.
你现在的样子真迷蛇
You are so hot right now.
贪心蛇 啥
- Snake! - Yeah?
来吧 伙计
Come on, man.
你们爬行动物真够变态的
You are one twisted reptile.
我真想留下来看场好戏
I wish I could stick around to see how it ends,
但我们还有火箭要偷
but we've got a rocket to steal.
再见
Ciao.
凯蒂豹 凯蒂豹 等等 等一下 求你了
Kitty. Kitty, wait. Hold on a second, please.
看吧 这就是为什么我不喜欢猫
See? This is why I'm not a cat person.
我们该怎么选
How are we supposed to choose?
我们不用选 我不会那么容易放弃
We're not. I don't give up that easy.
食人鱼 嗯
- Piranha. - Yeah?
我需要你拔出u盘 听我指令
I need you to pull out the USB. Follow my lead.
没问题 兄弟
You got it, papito.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
? Whole crowd ?
? Hold on, Boosie, wipe me down... ?
我拿到了
I got it!
上传速度越来越快了
And it's going faster.
不好 改计划 重组
- Not good. - New plan. Regroup!
? On the corner posted up, smoking loud ?
? Ay, tell 'em they can't break me, break me down ?
? Ay, come on, baby, shut it down ?
? Black king, black rose, black hoodie ?
? Black ..., black cars, got my Black chin up ?
? Tell 'em they can never bring us down ?
? Yeah, jumped off the porch since a child ?
? Why they wanna push me... ?
骇客蛛 你的腿困住了 还有足够的活动空间来黑系统吗
Webs, you got enough wiggle in those legs to hack in?
给我三条腿就够了 差不多
Three legs is all I need. I think.
那好 我们走
All right, let's go.
? All black on, got my ski mask ?
? All black on ?
? Got my ski mask... ?
大坏狼 大坏狼 我没黑进去
Wolf, Wolf, I can't get in.
快撤 快撤
Fall back! Fall back!
? Whew, girl, look at you ?
? Hop up in that coupe, check the temperature ?
? Hop up in that, hey, hey ?
? Star ..., mosh pit, they can never stop ... ?
? Got it from the mud, I ain't have no other option ?
? Watch out for the cops, here they come ?
? Gotta go ?
? Chain swang, Levi's, pain behind these eyes ?
? They don't want the...
? And I see why... ?
别着急 再想一想 再想一想
Now, think, think, think, think, think, think.
你能行的 你有办法的
You got this. You got this.
我们还能干嘛 我们还能干嘛
What are we doing? What are we doing?
? Now listen... ?
那个锻造炉 那个什么
- The forge! - The what?
我们要把电脑扔进火里
We're gonna throw the whole thing into the fire.
这是我们最后的机会 你行的 伙计
- It's our last chance. - You got this, buddy.
准备好
Here...
预备
we...
走
go!
? All black on, got my ski mask ?
? Hundred million ..., don't they see that? ?
? This not time for your feedback, ah ?
? All black on, got my ski mask ?
? All black on ?
? Got my ski mask ?
? Hundred million ..., don't they see that? ?
好吧 好吧
Well, well, well.
没有你的热狗卡车  就不那么厉害了吧 大坏狼
Not so tough without your hot dog truck, are you, Wolf?
这下梦想成真了
This is getting real.
早上好 女士们
Morning, ladies.
州长女士
Madam Governor.
哦 是啊 狐狸州长 对吧
Oh, yeah. Foxenstein, right?
很接近了
Close enough.
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
你知道我都是亲力亲为
You know, I'm very hands-on.
尤其当有人试图陷害我朋友的时候
Especially when someone tries to frame my friends.
我什么都知道了 反黄金 吸金石
I know everything. The MacGuffinite. The magnet.
嗯 你和橘子酱谈过了
Hmm. You talked to Marmalade.
事实上大部分时间都是他一个人在说
Actually, he did most of the talking.
我更喜欢直接动手
I'm more of an action girl.
让开 否则我会让你吃尽苦头
Step aside before anger becomes punch.
你们都被捕了
You're all under arrest.
州长的命令
Governor's orders.
哦 真有活力
Ooh, feisty.
你不知道 是吗
You don't know, do you?
你不再是州长了
You're not governor anymore.
你可能想看看 你的手机
You might want to check your phone.
深红魔爪
Crimson Paw.
深红…什么
Crimson... What?
不 不 不 但是…
No. No, no, no, no, no. But...
怎么 怎…怎么会
How-- H-How?
他们从不提防飞镖
They never expect the dart.
我们走吧
Shall we?
凯蒂豹
Kitty!
Kitty.
一段病毒式传播的视频显示臭名昭著的窃贼
A viral video has revealed that the notorious thief
深红魔爪
known as the Crimson Paw was
竟是州长黛安·福克斯顿
none other than Governor Diane Foxington! -
在警方搜寻这位骗子政客的同时
While police search for the rogue politician,
他们也没有浪费时间 立即释放了
they have wasted no time in ordering the speedy release
被陷害且可爱的橘子酱教授
of sweet, adorable Professor Marmalade,
他不像坏蛋联盟  那些家伙自称“改过自新”
unlike the Bad Guys, whose claim to have "changed"
现在完全没人相信
fooled absolutely no one.
警长 我们被一群 超级罪犯陷害了
Chief, we were set up by a gang of supercriminals.
他们把反黄金 变成了吸金磁铁
They turned the MacGuffinite into a gold magnet.
排好队 他们正在偷
- Back in line. - And they're stealing
那枚火箭把它带到太空
that rocket to take it to space.
是啊 他们都这么说
Yeah, that's what they all say.
警长 我知道这看起来很糟  但如果真的是我们干的
Ch-Chief, I know it looks bad, but if we did this,
我们为什么要帮你破案
why would we help you solve the case?
我们为什么要告诉你关于反黄金的事
Why would we tell you about the MacGuffinite?
而且赃物在哪儿呢 你知道这不合逻辑
And where's the loot? You know it doesn't add up.
听着 我们没有证据
Look, we don't have proof,
但我知道在你那颗强大澎湃的内心深处
but I know, somewhere in that big, booming heart of yours,
你知道这不是我们干的
you know we didn't do this.
警长 求你了
Chief, please.
我要告诉你多少次  大坏狼
How many times do I have to tell you, Wolf?
叫我“局长”
It's "Commissioner."
准备好驾驶这个了吗
Ready to fly this thing?
有了手表 火箭自己飞
With watch, rocket flies itself.
嘿 珍妮 你看到这个了吗
Hey, Jenny. You seeing this?
食人鱼街也别想了
So much for Piranha Street.
警长
Chief?
好吧 假设  我假设我相信你们
Okay, let's say, hypothetically, I believe you--
但我并不信
Which I don't.
但如果我信…如果我信真的有某个超级罪犯
But if I did... if I did and some supercriminal
拥有一个吸金磁铁  那我们怎么阻止他们
has a gold magnet, how would we stop them?
你…你相信我们
You... you believe us?
不 不
No! No, no, no!
No! No!
我想给她一个拥抱
I want to give her a hug.
哦 我喜欢警长
Ooh, I like Chief.
警长  那是新洗发水吗
Ooh, wow, Chief, is that a new shampoo?
好了 好了
Okay, okay.
请不要再摸了
Please stop with the touching.
我搞不懂你们
I don't get you guys.
你们是好人 然后是坏人 然后又有点像好人
You're good, then you're bad, then you're sort of good,
然后又是十足的坏人
then really bad.
呃 真难跟上你们的节奏
Ugh, it's hard to keep up!
是的 是的 这很正常
Yep, yep. That's fair.
我明白 我们变化无常
I get it. We're all over the place.
但你得在那枚火箭起飞前 把我们送到那里
But you need to get us to that rocket before it takes off.
火箭 什…什么 你说什么
Rocket? What-what are you talking about?
开始倒数
Initiating backwards counting.
倒计时已启动
Countdown initiated.
倒计时已启动 哇哦 怎么回事
Countdown initiated? Whoa. What's going on?
我不知道 嗯 关掉它 珍妮
- I don't know. - Well, shut it down, Jenny!
关掉它 我在试 吉姆
- Shut it down! - I'm trying, Jim!
呃 月亮先生
Uh, Mr. Moon?
呃 我们有点 小状况
Uh, we've got a slight situation.
发射不是要到 下周才
The launch isn't until next wee--
嗯 我的天哪
Well, butter my crumpets.
五 四…
Five, four...
疏散
Evacuate!
…三 二 一
...three, two, one.
呜呼
Woo-hoo!
反转接二连三
The twists just keep coming.
月亮X号火箭似乎 提前三天起飞了
The MoonX rocket seems to have taken off three days early--
搞什么鬼
What the hairbrush?
放马过来
Bring it on!
我的天哪
Holy moly.
你确定要这么做
Are you sure about this?!
不是很确定 不
Not particularly. No.
记住 当你们回来时  你们都被捕了
Remember, when you come back, you're under arrest!
知道了…局长
You got it... Commissioner.
去吧 伙计们
Go get 'em, guys.
好了 我们走
All right, here we go.
凡事都有 第一次 对吧
First time for everything, right?
快跑 跑我们走 来吧
- Run, run, run! Let's go! - Come on!
走 走
Go! Go! Go!
-我们走 走 走 -伙计们 快
- Let's go, go, go, go, go! - Guys, come on!
动起来 动起来
Move, move, move!
我们成功了 我们成功了 -耶
We did it. We did it. We did it. Yeah!
我们成功了
- Woo-hoo! - We did it!
我们还没成功
We didn't do it.
跳啊
Jump!
把我们拉上去 贪心蛇
Pull us up, Snake!
流瑜伽 宝贝
Vinyasa, baby!
在那儿 货舱
Up there! The cargo bay!
拉
Pull!
使劲拉 拉
Come on! Pull! Pull!
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?!
左松右紧
Lefty-loosey, righty-tighty.
哦 对了
Oh, right.
那是什么
What is it?
啊 没关系 只是个小故障
Ah, never mind. Just glitch.
景色真美
Now, that is a view.
怎么回事
What is happening?!
先生 他们正前往 多国空间站
Sir, they're heading to the Multinational Space Station.
我想他们正在对接
I think they're docking.
毒舌鸦 你跟我来
Doom, you're with me.
妙算猪 把反黄金放好
Pigtail, get the MacGuffinite in place.
知道了 凯蒂豹
You got it, Kitty.
有人在家吗
Yoo-hoo. Anybody home?
装修不错
Ooh, nice decor.
非常有太空感
Very, uh, space-y.
现在想想 刚才有点鲁莽了
In hindsight, that was a little reckless.
大家都没事吧
Did everybody make it?
嘿 食…食人鱼呢
Hey, wh-where's Piranha?
我会飞了
I can fly!
我只需要相信 自己 哈
I just needed to believe in myself. Ha!
哦 你… 你们也会飞
Oh, you... you guys can fly, too?
好了 小心腿
All right, watch the legs.
哇哦 伙计们 看这个
Whoa. Guys, check this out.
她在干什么
What is she doing?
他们正在使用 月亮X号能量电池
They're using the MoonX Power Cell
来激活反黄金
to activate the MacGuffinite.
真是天才
Kind of genius.
是啊 他们很聪明
Yeah, they're smart,
但有件事他们没料到
but there's something they didn't count on.
我有个计划
I got a plan.
安装完成
Mm-hmm. Installation complete.
确认坐标
Confirming coordinates.
我们不该…呃…为这个接受些特殊训练吗
Shouldn't we, uh, get some special training for this?
别…别往下看就行
Just don't-don't look down.
呃 追加一个问题：哪边是下
Uh, follow-up question: Which way is down?
听好了
Listen up.
这全靠时机
This is all about timing.
骇客蛛 美肚鲨 我需要你们黑进外部控制台
Webs, Shark, I need you to hack the external console
同时贪心蛇和食人鱼打开控制面板启动
while Snake and Piranha pop the control panel to engage
手动超控开关 知道了
- the manual override switch. - You got it.
那凯蒂豹呢 她交给我
- And what about Kitty? - Leave her to me.
我们只有一次机会拯救世界
We got one shot to save the world.
别搞砸了
Let's make it count.
好了 伙计 你能行的
Okay, buddy. You can do this.
首先 清空根目录 嗯哼
- First, clear the root folder. - Mm-hmm.
然后在系统目录里输入
Then in system directory, type
“ENC_word=word.encode”
"ENC underscore word equals word dot encode." -Mm-hmm.
现在输入“import hashlib”
Now "import hashlib."
嗯哼 按回车
- Mm-hmm. - Hit enter.
然后是“input_path=input”
Then "input underscore path equals input."
好的 酷 酷 知道了
Okay. Cool, cool. Got it.
好的 所以 你说清空根目录
Okay, so, clear the root folder, you say.
好了 来吧 来吧 食人鱼
Okay, come on. Come on, Piranha.
你不紧张 对吧
You're not nervous, right?
因为我们知道你紧张时会发生什么
'Cause we know what happens when you're nervous.
我…我有什么好紧张的
Wh-What would I be nervous about?
哦 食人鱼
Oh. Piranha!
伙计 抱歉
- Dude! - Sorry.
我能尝到
I can taste it.
我们已就位
We're in position.
我想是时候我们该自我介绍了
I think it's time we introduced ourselves.
? People, people, dancing on the people... ?
? People, people... ?
? Everybody... ?
? Apart from you ?
? Now that we're dancing ?
? People ?
? Dancing people ?
? Dancing people... ?
哦 谢谢
Oh. Thank you.
怎么回事 我怎么在飞
What's going on? Why am I flying?
我的天哪
Holy potatoes.
居然真的有用
It's actually working.
哦 耶
Ooh, yeah!
哦 天哪
Oh, boy.
我们怎么样了 贪心蛇 等一下
- How we doing, Snake? - Hang on.
搞定了
Got it!
就像偷糖果和一个婴儿
Like stealing candy and a baby.
你不是想说“从婴儿手里偷糖果”吗
Don't you mean "candy from a baby"?
我知道我说了什么
I know what I said.
气闸门怎么样了
How about the air lock?
好了 骇客蛛 我喜欢你的风格
All right, Webs. I like your style.
哦 那个全是美肚鲨干的
Oh, that one was all Shark.
我慌了
I panicked.
但结果不错 我现在是程序员了
But it worked out. I'm a programmer now.
我进去了
I'm going in.
那是什么 啊
- What was that? - Huh?
哦 那可不妙
Oh, that's not good.
贪心蛇 伙计 对不起
Snake, buddy, I'm sorry.
什么 不 不…
What? No, no, no...
我恨你
I hate you.
去气闸门
Get to the air lock!
走 走
Go, go, go!
姑娘们 现在没什么能阻止我们了
Girls, nothing gonna stop us now.
贪心蛇宝贝
Snakey Cakes?
救…我
Help... me.
别放屁了 你这个疯子
Stop farting, you maniac!
哇 哇 别这样
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Come on.
关掉它 好吗 你会杀了他们的
Turn it off, all right? You're gonna kill them.
不好意思 你站哪边的
I'm sorry. Whose side are you on?
凯蒂豹 住手 这只是次抢劫
Kitty, stop! It's just a heist.
抢劫从来都不只是抢劫
It's never just a heist!
锁住气闸门 现在
Secure the air lock. Now.
遵命 老大
Whatever you say, boss.
“关掉它 ”
"Turn it off."
哈 我才刚开始呢
Ha! I'm just getting started.
这简直是彻底的混乱
It is total mayhem!
一场灾难性的黄金风暴简直在摧毁这座城市
A cataclysmic gold storm is literally destroying the city!
哦 耶
Oh, yeah.
黄金
The gold.
来妈妈这儿
Come to mama.
你知道 我一直在想 -
You know, I've been thinking. -
大坏狼
Wolf?
那个词听起来不是有点像编的吗
Doesn't that word sound kind of made-up?
“黄金 ”有点怪 对吧
"Gold." It's kind of weird, right?
很怪 很怪 这是个很怪的词
- It's weird. It's weird-- It's a weird word.
来吧 说…说 “黄金 ”
Go ahead. S-Say, say, "Gold."
黄金 黄金 黄金
Gold. Gold. Gold.
总之 不重要了
Anyway, it doesn't matter.
我需要你关掉磁铁
I'm gonna need you to turn off the magnet.
或者我帮你关
Or I'll just do it for you.
这很好笑吗
Is that supposed to be funny?
坚持住 伙计
Stay with me, papo.
坚持住
Stay with me!
我…我不想这么死
I-I don't want to die like this.
好了 好了
Okay, okay.
来吧 食人鱼 你的朋友在太空中打转
Come on, Piranha, your friend is spinning out in space.
你应该知道该怎么做
You should know what to do.
对了 那支笔
That's it! The pen!
那支笔 什么…
The pen? Wha...
抓住那支笔 那支笔 抓住… -
Grab the pen! The pen! Grab the... -
哦 不 不
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
好的 我能做点事 我能做点事
Okay, I can do stuff. I can do stuff.
你为什么要冒着生命危险去救那些甚至不给你
Why would you risk your life to save people who wouldn't even
机会的人
give you a chance?
至少当你还是大坏狼的时候  他们尊重你
At least when you were the Big Bad Wolf, they respected you.
哦 那是尊重 嗯
Oh, that was respect, huh?
那不是尊重 那是恐惧
That wasn't respect. That was fear.
哦 无所谓 伙计
Oh, whatever, man.
有什么区别
What's the difference?
相信我 有区别
Trust me, there's a difference.
尊重是赢得的
Respect is earned.
总有一天 你会明白的
One day, you'll learn that.
说真的 大坏狼 你凭什么觉得这会成功
Honestly, Wolf, what made you think this would work?
谁说没成功
Who says it didn't?
就像你说的 重点不是行动
Like you said, it's not about the action.
是分散注意力
It's about the distraction.
嘿 天才 手表控制的是穿梭机  不是磁铁
Hey, genius, the watch controls the shuttle, not the magnet.
你懂的
You get it.
她懂的
She gets it.
拿到了
Got it!
你确定吗
You sure about this?
相信我 小子
Trust me, chico.
金枪鱼之力
Tuna power!
我拿到了
I got it!
干得好 伙计们 骇客蛛 告诉我你准备好了
Well done, boys. Webs, tell me you're ready.
正在对准 大坏狼
Lining it up, Wolfie.
干得不错 孩子
Nice work, kid.
不
No.
你想看实力展示吗 凯蒂豹
You want to see a power move, Kitty?
这才是实力展示
This is a power move.
没事
It's fine.
啊 喂
- -Huh? - Hello!
需要帮忙吗 我来帮你 贪心蛇宝贝
- Need a hand? - I got you, Snakey Cakes.
哦 甜心鸟
Oh, Sugar Beak.
你还说你不喜欢我
And you said you weren't into me.
你为什么会相信我说的任何话
Why would you believe anything I say?
不
No!
没有穿梭机 你怎么回地球
How do you expect to get back to Earth without a shuttle?!
至少还有个地球可以回去…
At least there's an Earth to go back...
你毁了我的完美计划
You destroyed my beautiful plan!
我告诉过你别惹我朋友了吧
What did I tell you about messing with my friends?
什…你怎么… 大坏狼 我们拿…哦
- Wha-- How did you... - Wolf, we got-- Oh.
我们试过阻止她发…
We tried to stop her from posting...
啊 哇哦 中等友好关系怎么了
Ah, wow. What happened to medium friendly?
嗯 幸好我不再是州长了 对吧
Well, good thing I'm not the governor anymore, huh?
呃 恶心
Ugh, gross.
是时候了 伙计们
- 'Bout time. - Guys!
哇哦 黛安狐
Whoa! Diane.
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
碰巧在绕地球轨道飞行
Just happened to be orbiting the Earth.
想着顺道来看看
Thought I'd drop by.
呜呼 -耶
Woo-hoo! -Yeah!
我们成功了 宝贝
We did it, baby.
我感受到了爱 真的 我感受到了
I feel the love. Like, I feel it.
我这辈子都在听说著名的坏蛋联盟
I hear about the famous Bad Guys all my life.
但现在我明白了
But now I get it.
警报
Alert.
系统大规模故障 警报
- It is a massive system failure. - Alert.
我们正在脱离轨道
We're falling out of orbit.
我想就到这了 大坏狼
I think this is it, Wolfie.
我们完蛋了
We're doomed!
最后拥抱一下 各位
One last hug, everybody?
哇 哇 哇 哇 哇 等等
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Hang on.
别那么说
Don't talk like that.
当然 这…看起来…是的 很糟
Sure, it's-- it looks-- yeah, it's bad.
是啊 好吧 很糟
Yeah, okay. It's bad.
当然 我们正坐着一个铁罐子冲向地球
Sure, we're hurtling towards Earth in a tin can,
直面死亡
staring squarely into the face of death.
当然 我们的血液可能会沸腾 骨骼可能会液化
Sure, our blood may boil, our bones may liquefy,
但如果我了解这个团队的一件事
but if there's one thing that I know about this crew,
那就是我们永不 永不放弃
it's that we never, ever give up.
因为我们拥有比恐惧更强大的东西
Because we have something that's stronger than fear,
甚至比重力更强大
stronger than even gravity.
那就是希望
And that's hope.
是啊 希望
Yeah, hope.
那就是希望
That's hope.
我们要把这东西降落…
We're gonna land this thing...
…或者我们会死在尝试上
...or we're gonna die tryi--
那些家伙
What those guys,
那些勇敢 美丽的家伙在上面所做的
those brave, beautiful guys did up there,
将世界从一场24K金的大灾难中拯救出来
saving the world from a 24-karat catastrophe.
尽管遭受了所有的拒绝和怀疑
And despite all the rejection and suspicion,
所有微小的羞辱 他们都是为了我们做的
all the tiny humiliations, they did it for us.
他们不是为了名声或荣耀
They didn't do it for the fame or for the glory.
他们是为了我们
They did it for us.
他们不仅仅是好人
They weren't just good guys.
他们是我最好的朋友
They were my best friends.
我愿意付出一切 只为再逮捕他们
And I would give anything to arrest them
一次
just one more time.
这个敬你 大坏狼
This one's for you, Wolfie!
我个人感到愤怒 居然要等到一个邪恶的太空磁铁
I, for one, am outraged that it took an evil space magnet
才让人们意识到坏蛋联盟
for people to realize that the Bad Guys
一直都值得我们去爱
were worthy of our love all along.
但现在太晚了 因为他们已经死了
But it's too late, because now they're dead.
讽刺的是劫案的
Ironically, the only survivors
唯一的幸存者
were the perpetrators of the heist,
包括被称为幻影大盗的超级罪犯
including the supercriminal known as the Phantom Bandit,
而不幸的是第二个逃生舱是空的
while a second escape pod was, tragically, empty.
我演得怎么样
Did I sell it or did I sell it?
你要告诉我们这到底是怎么回事吗
Are you gonna tell us what this is all about?
是啊 因为我没感觉自己会死
Yeah, 'cause I don't feel dead.
那些穿西装的是谁
And who are the suits?
为什么还要在室内戴墨镜
And why are they wearing sunglasses inside?
我知道 我知道这看起来很复杂 但相信我
I know. I know it seems elaborate, but trust me,
如果你想做些真正的好事 这就是最好的方法
it's the best way if you want to do some serious good.
先生们 女士们
Gentlemen. Ladies.
你们已被确定为加入一个全新的
You have been identified as ideal candidates
超精英的秘密特工组织的理想人选
for a brand-new, ultra-elite unit of secret operatives
我们称之为
that we're calling the International
国际超星系守护者联盟
Super-Galactic League of Protectors:
超联
ISGLOP.
这名字听起来有点像编出来的
- Huh? - Sounds kind of made-up.
我…我不明白 现在什么情况
I-I don't understand. What-What's happening?
你们有新身份了 孩子们
We're offering you a job, son.
你们要当秘密特工了
You're gonna be secret agents!
认真的吗 不可能吧
- Is he serious? - That can't be right.
秘密特工 别开玩笑了
Secret agents? Get out of here.
他们好像是认真的 真的吗 我就说嘛
- They're serious? Really? - That's what I'm talking about!
-太好了 没问题
- Woo-hoo! -Nice. - All right.
嘿 差点忘了你还在
Hey. Almost forgot you were there.
你可能已经注意到了 改变并不容易
As you might have noticed, change isn't easy.
有时候你会感觉自己完全没有希望了
Some days, it's gonna feel downright hopeless.
但只要有好心态
But with the right attitude
和好朋友
and the right friends,
总有一天 美好的生活会来临的
the good life has a way of finding you.
准备好开工了吗 大坏狼特工
Ready to get to work, Agent Wolf?
这样也不错
Not bad.
一点都不错
Not bad at all.
别走开 精彩继续
Power by Love
Beta
? I feel lucky, and I feel blessed ?
? The sun is shining, so take a breath ?
? Of the good life, good life ?
? We heading for the good life ?
? Good li-i-i-ife ?
? Cool breeze blowing away my cares ?
? 'Cause where we're going, it's in the air ?
? It's the good life, good life ?
? We heading for the good life ?
? Good li-i-i-ife ?
? Oh, so good, just the way it should be ?
? Told you that it could be, told you that we would be ?
? Heading for some new heights ?
? Heading for the high life ?
? Feels like we just took flight ?
? We on a joyride ?
? Never doubted we were born for greatness ?
? A life so animated that nothing can contain it ?
? Leveled up like we knew all the levels from the start ?
? I hope you feeling like a star ?
? We're gonna show the whole world who we are ?
? All those days we were searching for ?
? Something meaningful, something more ?
? Like the good life, good life ?
? We were longing for the good life ?
? Good li-i-i-ife ?
? I knew we'd get here, never doubted, never doubted it ?
? If we are in a dream, then I ain't coming out of it ?
? Speeding through the clouds ?
? So you better hold on, grip tight ?
? Ready for the spotlight, we heading for the good life ?
? I feel lucky ?
? And I feel blessed ?
? The sun is shining ?
? So take a breath of ?
? The good life, good life ?
? We heading for the good life ?
? Good li-i-i-ife ?
? The sun is out, so am I ?
? Let's get our wings on to fly ?
? I feel the magic around ?
? Nobody stopping us now ?
? With you here by my side ?
? I can feel where we can glide ?
? So much higher than the sky ?
? Oh, oh ?
? We heading for ?
? The good life, yeah ?
? The good life ?
? Uh-uh ?
? We heading for ?
? The good life ?
? Good life, good life ?
? Get ready for the good life ?
? Good life ?
? We heading for the good life ?
? Uh-uh, we heading for the good life ?
? It's the good, it's the good ?
? It's the good life ?
? Good life, good life ?
? Get ready for the good life, good life ?
? We heading for the good life, good life ?
? Get ready for the good life ?
? Good li-i-i-ife ?
? Good life ?
? Good life, good life... ?
我就喜欢计划成功的感觉
I love it when a plan comes together.
现在是时候回家了
And now time to go home.
? You ain't courageous enough ?
?Most of you probably fold ?  ?Yeah ?
? You ain't willing to the face the challenge ?
?Acquire the gold ?  ?Yeah ?
? We only here to just retrieve what you probably stole ?
? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ?
? You see, steel sharpen steel ?
?When it's time for the go ?  ?Yeah ?
? We here to create such a ruckus ?
?We all on a roll ?  ?Yeah ?
? Stare every challenge in the eye ?
? We don't play with the soul ?
? No matter what you was told, every rat find a hole ?
? See, it don't matter what you thought ?
? Yeah, yeah, yeah ?
? We taking everything you want ?
? Whoa, whoa, whoa ?
? Now don't forget it, better know we come to get it ?
? And we with it and there's nothing better ?
? I hope you know to play it smart ?
? See all the greatness when we come ?
?When the story is told ?  ?Yeah ?
? Can't put a timeline on greatness ?
?It never gets old ?  ?Yeah ?
? Come get the scope when we hot and you not ?
? And we pull up and we come in ?
? Taking everything you got, ugh ?
? See, it don't matter what you thought ?
? Yeah, yeah, yeah ?
? We taking everything you want ?
? Whoa, whoa, whoa ?
? Now don't forget it, better know we come to get it ?
? And we with it and there's nothing better ?
? I hope you know to play it smart ?
? No matter what you thought, you better believe ?
?We coming ?  ?Yeah ?
? And if you thought that we was playing ?
?Let me show you something ?  ?Yeah ?
? So then we jump and we swoop ?
? And we dodge every bullet ?
? It don't matter when they pull up ?
? And they try to pull it ?
? Pull it ?
? Better know we on the clock ?
?And it's time to go ?  ?Yeah ?
? Everything is tactical ?
?Now enjoy the show ?  ?Yeah ?
? Then we skip and we bounce ?
? And we hop out of every situation ?
? Best believe that it's time to blow ?
? See, it don't matter what you thought ?
? Yeah, yeah, yeah ?
? We taking everything you want ?
? Whoa, whoa, whoa ?
? Now don't forget it, better know we come to get it ?
? And we with it and there's nothing better ?
? I hope you know to play it smart ?
? Smart ?
? You know the heat melt ?
? Better wear your seat belt and strap up ?
? You know we get a little crazy ?
? Every single time we act up ?
? I know the way you see us doing it to 'em ?
? I think you really, really need to shack up ?
? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ?
? It don't matter every single time they really try ?
? To trap us, and they come from every corner ?
? And they really try to catch us, we're completing ?
? Every mission no matter how they attack us, and the fact ?
? Is that we back and that we never, never slack up ?
? Better get up out the way because we come and then ?
? We pack up, and we taking everything you want ?
? You know you better back up ?
? Let's go. ?
那 再见咯…
Well, bye...!